<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="bases_title">Psychosophical bases</string>

    <string name="bases_info_will"><![CDATA[
    \t<b><i>Will</i></b> — sense of having an aim, a meaning of human existence, his place in the world, perception of life purposes and desires.<br>
    \tWill is the kernel of the personality, its motive force, which forces to change other components of the world.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="bases_info_logic"><![CDATA[
    \t<b><i>Logic</i></b>  — a world of ideas, of all that is the product of the activity of the mind of man. It does not matter whether they have material embodiment or not.<br>
    \tThe position of Logic determines the degree of subjective value of inferences, beauty and completeness of ideas and concepts.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="bases_info_emotion"><![CDATA[
    \t<b><i>Emotion</i></b> — sphere of inner experiences of a person: feelings, emotions.<br>
    \tIn addition, Emotion is responsible for the attitude to the art and beauty of the surrounding world in general.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="bases_info_physics"><![CDATA[
    \t<b><i>Physics</i></b> — the world of everything material.<br>
    \tThe position of the physicist is responsible for the attitude to own body and its needs, the importance of owning material goods,
     physical labor and work in general, for biological aggressiveness and readiness for the violent resolution of conflicts.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="functions_title">Functions on psychosophy</string>

    <string name="functions_info_first"><![CDATA[
    \t<b><i>I. \"Hammer\"</i></b> is a basic human function. On it, he is most sure of himself and sees it as the most valuable.<br>
    \tIn the field of this function, a person often manifests himself excessively, not noticing the reaction of others.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="functions_info_second"><![CDATA[
    <b><i>II. \"River\"</i></b></i> is a normative function.<br>
    \tThe most moderate and harmonious, knows how to relate their interests in this area to the interests of the surrounding people.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="functions_info_third"><![CDATA[
    <b><i>III. \"Sore\"</i></b> is painful, restless, uncertain.<br>
    \tOn the one hand, a person feels the need to prove himself in this area, on the other, he is not confident in his abilities and is afraid of criticism and negative evaluation.<br>
    \tIn addition, this function clearly sees the shortcomings of others in this field and willingly criticizes them.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="functions_info_forth"><![CDATA[
    \t<b><i>IV. \"Trifle\"</i></b> is the least significant for a person and therefore calm and detached.<br>
    \tOften, according to it, a person does not have his own preferences in this area and easily adapts to others.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="functions_info"><![CDATA[
    \tAll functions can be divided according to three criteria:
    <b><i>the productive</i></b> (<b>I</b> and <b>IV</b>) and <b><i>the processional</i></b> (<b>II</b> and <b>III</b>, where <b> III </ b> is the super processional);
    <b><i>the dominant</i></b> (<b>I</b> and <b>III</b>) and <b><i>the adjusting</i></b> (<b>II</b> and <b>IV</b>);
    <b><i>the high</i></b> (<b>I</b> and <b>II</b>) and <b><i>the low</i></b> (<b>III</b> and <b>IV</b>).
    ]]></string>

</resources>