<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="first_function_title">I</string>
    <string name="second_function_title">II</string>
    <string name="third_function_title">III</string>
    <string name="forth_function_title">IV</string>

    <string name="common_description_title">General description</string>
    <string name="functions_at_position_hint">Learn more</string>

    <string name="first_emotion_name">I Emotion (romantic)</string>
    <string name="first_emotion_short_name">I EMOTION</string>
    <string name="second_emotion_name">II Emotion (actor)</string>
    <string name="second_emotion_short_name">II EMOTION</string>
    <string name="third_emotion_name">III Emotion (rusk)</string>
    <string name="third_emotion_short_name">III EMOTION</string>
    <string name="forth_emotion_name">IV Emotion (gawkers)</string>
    <string name="forth_emotion_short_name">IV EMOTION</string>
    <string name="first_logic_name">I Logics (dogmatist)</string>
    <string name="first_logic_short_name">I LOGIC</string>
    <string name="second_logic_name">II Logics (ritor)</string>
    <string name="second_logic_short_name">II LOGIC</string>
    <string name="third_logic_name">III Logics (skeptic)</string>
    <string name="third_logic_short_name">III LOGIC</string>
    <string name="forth_logic_name">IV Logics (pupil)</string>
    <string name="forth_logic_short_name">IV LOGIC</string>
    <string name="first_physics_name"> I Physics (owner)</string>
    <string name="first_physics_short_name"> I PHYSICS</string>
    <string name="second_physics_name">II Physics (toiler)</string>
    <string name="second_physics_short_name">II PHYSICS</string>
    <string name="third_physics_name">III Physics (touchy)</string>
    <string name="third_physics_short_name">III PHYSICS</string>
    <string name="forth_physics_name">IV Physics (sluggard)</string>
    <string name="forth_physics_short_name">IV PHYSICS</string>
    <string name="first_will_name">I Will (king)</string>
    <string name="first_will_short_name">I WILL</string>
    <string name="second_will_name">II Will (nobleman)</string>
    <string name="second_will_short_name">II WILL</string>
    <string name="third_will_name">III Will (bourgeois)</string>
    <string name="third_will_short_name">III WILL</string>
    <string name="forth_will_name">IV Will (serf)</string>
    <string name="forth_will_short_name">IV WILL</string>

    <string name="first_emotion_description"><![CDATA[
        \t\"Flood of feelings\", \"mental storm\", \"volcanic passion\" - all this \ "romantic\" is vested from birth.
        <i>Loud, contagious laughter, plentiful eruption of tears</i> - redundancy of the 1st emotion can easily infect a person with his mood.
        \"Romantic\" always expresses his feelings with a strong exaggeration, therefore, when talking with him, you often need to reset 20-30%
        of emotional glow in order to get a fairly accurate and clear picture of the experiences.
        <br><br>

        \tA charming description of the specific inadequacy of her 1st Emotion was given in one interview by American actress Liza Minnelli.
        <blockquote> <b>- Are your emotions simulated?</b><br>
                        - No, of course, but heavily powdered and painted. If I fall in love, I say the first evening:
                        "I can not live without you, do not disappear from my life."<br>
                        <b>- Are you lying?</b><br>
                        - This is all too mixed: yes and no. In the morning, if he leaves, I can forget about him and not remember all day.
                         And on the other hand, I really think that, if he's gone forever, I would die!</blockquote>

        \tFor \"romantic\" joy is not joy, but maniacal, sadness is not sadness, but depression.
        However, most of these experiences remain inside and only the echoes of states reach the surrounding people.
        It happens because <i> the 1st Emotion is not inclined to share feelings</i>, prefers to savor them alone, showing himself as an actor and a viewer in one person.
        <br><br>

        \tWhen the power of emotions of \"romantic\" reaches its peak (result), they are often ejected.
        And here, you can expect everything from him. The fact is that the forms of manifestation of the peak of the 1st Emotion are manifold.
        They can take an artistic form (poetry, painting, music, dance), after which glory, recognition, etc., often come,
        but they can not take shape, or rather, take the form of a stream of tears, incoherent or inarticulate cries.
        <br><br>

        \tTearfulness is the earliest sign of the first Emotion.
        However, the normal for \"romantic\" child reaction in crises and pressure from outside, which are tears,
        rarely is correctly understood by others. Moreover, it becomes the reason of teasing and contemptuous characteristics.
        And since nothing changes in the order of functions with the years of \"romantics\", then <i>the constant pressure on this trait is able to impose
        they having something like a complex of emotional supercompleteness.</i>
        <br><br>

        \tOne woman with such a \"complex\" wrote to the psychiatrist: <br><br>
        <blockquote>I cry over books and at the cinema, cry at the sounds of the orchestra, listening to the songs.
        It's enough to see a girl in a wreath on TV… The slightest trouble - and again tears. I already began to hate myself for them,
        I can not get rid of them, I feel somehow defective.</blockquote>

        \tConsolation to the author of the letter can be the circumstance that she is not alone in her sufferings,
        and even great people often could not cope with their crying.
        <i>\"Romantic\" is a poet. A poet even when he does not write poetry or writes at all.</i>
    ]]></string>

    <string name="second_emotion_description"><![CDATA[
        \tIn whatever tonality an \"actor\" express their feelings, whether in increased or reduced - it will always be adequate to the situation,
        will always go from fact to emotion, and not vice versa, as is usually done by the \"romantic\".
        The second e motion is a movie actor.
        Its immense dignity is a constant desire to enrich its own sense-palette.
        <br><br>

        \tThe unifying beginning of all the carriers of the 2nd emotion is the burning, never satiated appetite for all sorts of artistic and artistic products.
        The range here is huge: from memorizing thousands of sacred texts to a very serious gathering of anecdotes, speeches.
        A matter of taste and upbringing.
        But the principle is one: <i> the desire and opportunity, through the processing of artistic information, to be the soul of society. </i>
        <br><br>

        \tThe second Emotion can fend for itself. Anyone who has tried to present to the \"actor\" any accounts, to climb with his claims, usually very soon began to regret his idea.
        Because, after deduction of the second logic, only the second emotion masterfully mastered the art of eloquence.
        <br><br>

        \tLanguage - native, natural for the second Emotion element, and woe to someone who chooses it as the field of battle with the \"actor\".
        The accuracy of the word, the accuracy of expression - not a distant goal, but the normal state of the \"actor\", regardless of the cultural level.
        <br><br>

        \tWhen N.V. Gogol, remembering the obscene nickname of one of the heroes of \"Dead Souls\" and comparing in this connection the Russian language
        with other European languages, wrote that:
        <blockquote>But there is no word that would be so briskly so would break out from under the heart, so it would boil and quiver like a well-spoken Russian word.</blockquote>
        \tHe did not flatter the Russian people at all, but only stated the predominance of the second Emotion in his environment.
        <br><br>

        \tHowever, the reality is that if the \"actor\" is not engaged in the service of feelings - religious, mystical, artistic, entertaining -
        <i>society does not appreciate its talent </i>. Human life is such a thing that more is valued in it more physics, will, sometimes logic, but not emotion.
        Moreover, the owner of the second emotion in everyday life sometimes has to feel disgust and even dislike towards himself.
        This is because the second function is the best side of human nature, and if it is not in high demand in society,
        then the person willy-nilly turns to the people, not to say, bad, but not the best part of their personality.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="third_emotion_description"><![CDATA[
        \tThe third e motion is the most helpless thing in the world. There is no ethics, no right,
        capable at least hypothetically to take up the defense of \"rusk\" from the most painful blows for him: hysterics and generally emotional executions.
        Defenselessness of the third Emotion before the turbulent eruption of feelings is perceived by us as nothing more than an incident, eccentricity, but not a personal drama.
        But in vain.
        <br><br>

        \tHere is a true tragedy, doubly painful, because it is absolutely incomprehensible and invisible to others.
        In response to hysterical cries, the 3rd Emotion has time to clamp its ears and mutter: \"Take it, take everything, but, for God\'s sake, stop this… \"

        <blockquote>Only without emotions!</blockquote>
        \tThe phrase with which the \"rusk\" usually comes into conflict, even pronounced in a categorical tone, is in fact not a requirement,
        and a secret plea for indulgence towards weakness, a vain attempt to cover up a sore spot in the fight.
        <br><br>

        \tLeo Tolstoy, recreating the image of the unhappy Karenin in his famous novel, was strikingly accurate in looking after the third emotion.
        <blockquote> Nobody, except the closest people to Alexey Alexandrovich, did not know that this seemingly coldest and most reasonable man had one, contradictory to the general character, weakness.
        Alexey Alexandrovich could not indifferent to hear and see the tears of a child or a woman.
        The sight of tears led him into a confused state, and he lost completely the faculty of consideration.</blockquote>

        \t<i>\"Impenetrability\"</i> is the word that most accurately conveys the claims to the third Emotion from the people who are close to it.
        At the first acquaintance, this is rarely drawn attention, \"rusk\" are, in this situation, extremely comfortable, reliable, interesting people.
        In communication with them, there is no serious discomfort.
        <br><br>

        \tOtherwise, the situation develops with a serious rapprochement, not to mention the joint life.
        The impenetrability of the third Emotion reveals itself as a painful and even frightening feature.
        You can marry, raise children, build a house, and never know how the \"rusk\" treats you.
        <br><br>

        \tA blank wall of emotional inexpressiveness grows before everyone who needs to figure out the attitude towards himself.
        Only being close to the \"rusk\" you understand how important an instrument in behavior and relationships is emotion.
        And how it may be missed for the most elementary communication, how painfully experienced is the chronic impenetrability of the \"rusk\".
        <br><br>

        \tIn addition, that \"rusk\" rarely marries (getting married), he also rarely gets children.
        The source of the problem is the same - defenselessness before emotional pressure.
        Children have one means of influencing the world - a cry, and he is the most painful means of influence for the third emotion.
        The \"rusk\" itself is the ideal child. It is as if specially created for bad parents.
        <br><br>
    ]]></string>

    <string name="forth_emotion_description"><![CDATA[
        \tThe rank of \"gawker\" the fourth emotion got because talking about art products, it does not produce as much as consumes.
        Although among the \"gawkers\" artists are not uncommon (an example of the great Goethe will be here quite expressive), all the same in the artistic sphere
        they are more consumption-oriented other than creativity. \"Gawker\" is the best reader, listener, spectator.
        <br><br>

        \tHe <i> is omnivorous, mirror </i> in his artistic perception, therefore on whatever step of the functional hierarchy the emotion of the artist stood,
        he will always find a grateful and adequate response from the \"gawker\".
        <br><br>

        \tThe 4th emotion is emotionally non-party.
        And the thunder of the first emotion, and the spill of the second emotion, and the whisper of the third emotion - everything is accepted by a thin, sensitive soul \"gawker\".
        There is only quality for him, but not the style of the work, which often allows the 4th emotion to act in a role qualified and impartial critic.
        <br><br>

        \tThe remarkable property of the 4th emotion is that in the life of \"gawker\" there is a period when its sensitivity does not look at all the last
        in its internal hierarchy, but on the contrary - the first.
        Feeling of the 4th emotion as the 1st connected with the endocrine system and is bound by a special mode of operation
        hormonal mechanism, which falls on the adolescent period, i.e. the period between the 15th and 25th years.
        <br><br>

        \t\"Gawker\" is not emotionally free.
        And Napoleon, with his 4th emotion, often complained that the loved ones had adapted
        for the mercenary purposes of catching him for this dependent place. He spoke to the French diplomat Colencourt:
        <blockquote>I have often experienced this with Josefina, who constantly appealed to me with various requests and even caught me by surprise with her tears,
        at the sight of which I agreed to much, what should be refused.</blockquote>

        \tAt the same time, it would be extremely superficial to imagine the 4th emotion as a perfect emotional chameleon,
        absolutely colorless at the time of freedom from external emotional impact.
        Indeed, the 4th emotion is very dependent and weak in the face of another's expansion of feelings, but from this <i>it does not mean that it is soulless and blind.</i>
        <br><br>

        \tAnother thing is that it is rarely possible to find out what it is by itself - in moments of loneliness - only then it is revealed,
        what forces, depths and riches in it are hidden.
        One trouble: it does not happen often.
        Behind the wall the tape recorder is turned on, and the foot of the \"gawker\" involuntarily begins to beat the rhythm, in the yard a child bursts into tears,
        and the eyes of the \"gawker\" are moistened, the beautiful half of him bursts into the room with the furious cry, and immediately receives in response a rage equal in rage.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="first_logic_description"><![CDATA[
        \t\"Dogmatist\" may be a wise person, and an impenetrable dumbass.
        The first logic focuses on <i> the effectiveness of thinking </i>, and what are the results - this is a purely individual question.
        <br><br>

        \tAmong the external signs of the 1st logic, the most significant and indicative is the unequivocally affirmative form of communication.
        Monologue of the 1st logic is irresistible.
        Fortunately, \"dogmatist\" is not talkative, has the ability to hear and does not hurry to speak on any of the proposed topics.
        <br><br>

        \tHe allows himself to start a monologue only in comfortable conditions, i.e. in connection with the problems in which he considers himself competent.
        This manifests the prudence inherent in the first logic.
        Communicate outside the affirmative form, it can not, and the discovery during the cavalry assault the insolvency of its first - and the most powerful function - is fraught with self-destruction of the person.
        <br><br>

        \tAnother reason for the silence of the 1st logic is the lack of talent and taste to the discussion.
        In disputes with the \"dogmatist\" truth is not born, it is either asserted or rejected.
        Usually he goes to the debate with a cudgel of absolute truth, which sometimes very effectively jamming his opponent.
        <br><br>

        \t\"Dogmatist\" is generally a stayer, and not a sprinter of intelligence.
        Darwin admitted:<br><br>
        <blockquote>I am not endowed with the ability to grasp on the fly or the sharpness of the mind, which amazes us in gifted people, for example, in Huxley.
        Accordingly, I\'m not a good critic.</blockquote>

        \tThe third reason for the silence of the 1st logic: dislike of idle chatter, hypotheses and generally private opinion.
        \"Dogmatist\" is seeking an absolute truth, not opinion.
        Only absolute truth can be put by a brick in that intellectual support that the 1st Logic builds for itself.
        <br><br>

        \tHowever, even the \"dogmatist\" himself is the author of hypotheses.
        For the 1st logic, thought is primary and self-sufficient, it is objective and does not need any crutches.
        Go from concept to fact, and not vice versa - the usual way for the first logic of the action.
        It is natural for such an image of thought and for the fact that there is no more painful sight for the \"dogmatist\" than the kind of theory that has been struck by the fact.
        <br><br>

        \tOnce, when talking with Huxley about the nature of the tragic, someone mentioned Spencer.
        <blockquote>\"Ha!\" Cried Huxley, \"The tragedy in Spencer\'s view is deduction, which was mortified by the fact.\"</blockquote>

        \t\"Dogmatist\" reacts extremely sharply to any obvious stupidity, nonsense, alogism, rubbish, other logics perceived usually fairly lenient.
        Knowing nonsense, that is, direct mockery of the best, most important aspect of the psyche \"dogmatist\" almost immediately knocked him out of the rut,
        leading up to rabies, to hysterics.
        <br><br>

        \tThe thinking of the 1st logic may not be the best in the world, but, for sure, <i> the most honest</i> one.

        \tWe very much recognize the handwriting of \"dogmatist\".
        It is ugly, difficult to read and, according to his principles, approaches shorthand.
     ]]></string>

    <string name="second_logic_description"><![CDATA[
        \t\"Ritor\" is a great fan of talking.
        Communication is air and bread of the second logic.
        <br><br>

        \tThe secret of this art is in ability and desire not only to speak out, but, first of all,
        to involve the interlocutor in conversation, to make intellectual feast together.
        Method: to pretend to be a fool and start communicating with a phrase similar to the famous Socratic:

        <blockquote>I only know that I do not know anything.</blockquote>
        \tIt is hard to imagine who would refuse to swallow such a bait.
        <br><br>

        \tAnother wonderful and precious quality, characteristic of all \"ritors\" without exception is a healthy cynicism.
        The second logic does not believe in God, in the line, in the party programs, or in scientific doctrines - in anything.
        All the axiomatic, dogmatic, having got into the millstones of the cerebral hemispheres of the \"ritor\'s\" brain, quickly loses its absoluteness
        and becomes a mere object of intellectual manipulation.
        <br><br>

        \tFor the "ritor" there are no prohibitions, no frames, no rules that keep the free game of thought.
        Everyone is subject to the trial of the second logic, but this court is gracious and seldom makes the final verdict (except that she is obviously stupid).
        The sentence is the result, the end of the process, which is so dear to the 2-nd logic.
        Therefore, the cynicism of her statements is devoid of aggressive, categorical notes, it is the cynicism of a non-party, free-thinking person.
        <br><br>

        \tTo refute today what was said yesterday is the normal state of the "ritor".
        You do not have to go far for an example - Lenin.
        <blockquote>
        During his life, he talked so much of the opposite that the Leninists still can not decide,
        which of his statements should be considered directives.
        A great polemicist, Lenin always managed to make an extremely convincing thought, directly contradicting the one,
        which he still defended with no less brilliance.</blockquote>

        \tIt is impossible not to admire the breadth of the interests of the 2nd Logic.
        He does not know the equal of the second logic and as a commentator, interpreter of other people's ideas.
        <br><br>

        \tThe only, perhaps, disadvantage of the second logic, which is a continuation of its advantages,
        is that the thinking of the \"ritor\" tends toward tactics rather than strategy.
        \"Ritor\" is not great in writing out his own views.
        And this is understandable.
        <i>His passion is living communication, and not a battle with a dead sheet of paper.</i>
        The only thing when the 2nd logic willingly turns to paper is during compelled loneliness.
        Just being doomed to silence, it turns to such a surrogate as paper.
        <br><br>

        \tAnother notable and fun feature of the nature of the 2nd logic is the passion to make notes in books, especially library books.
        Reading with a pencil, it abundantly equips pages with features, exclamation and question marks, etc.
        Usually the phenomenon of passion for chirping in books is explained in two ways: either lack of culture, or a desire to more firmly capture
        the most important places in memory.
        But in reality the origins of this passion are different.
        The notes in the books are typical of the 2nd logic <i> form of communication</i>, the message to all future nameless owners of the book,
        an attempt to exchange opinions in absentia.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="third_logic_description"><![CDATA[
        \tThe title of \"skeptic\" deserves any holder of the 3rd logic, regardless of the level of education and the degree of philosophical preparation.
        The usual, everyday \"skeptic\" - is a silent, very cautious person in the premises and conclusions,
        with hostility and irony related to all sorts of categorical judgments.
        <br><br>

        \tExperiencing an almost panic fear of an acute, gambling dispute, \"skeptic\", at the same time, like no one,
        appreciates a leisurely, benevolent, free-flowing conversation in which there are no winners and losers,
        and therefore, there is no <i> division into clever and fools </i> (getting into the last group the 3rd logic is afraid most of all).
        <br><br>

        \tIt appreciates, frankly speaking, meaningless chatter, in which the process is much more valuable than the result.
        Here it is found out that the alleged silent is in fact monstrously verbose, that there is no greater joy for it,
        than quietly, almost in a whisper, murmur and murmur, sorting, like the beads of the beads, theme by theme.
        <br><br>

        \tThinking of the third logic is a kind of labyrinth in which <i>all paths are equally acceptable, but there is no way out.</i>
        Special topic is the relationship actual thinking and the speech.
        The key here can serve as the phrase of one owner of the 3rd logic:
        <blockquote>I can not think and speak at the same time.</blockquote>

        \tBetween the intellectual product and its implementation, gaps are constantly formed,
        they have to fill up with all kinds of garbage to hide the defect.
        Therefore, one of the characteristic features of the third logic is the abundance of all sorts of weird words in speech.
        Interjections, mooing and similar attempts exists to gain some time for deliberation, and giving the effect of continuous speech flow.
        <br><br>

        \tThe idea of the feelings experienced by the third logic, when it is at the department,
        give excerpts from one letter to a psychiatrist:
        <blockquote>I teach at a technical college.
        For the sixth month I've been lecturing in my specialty.
        \"I teach\" - it is said incorrectly.
        I do not teach, but I suffer and torment listeners.
        I go out to listeners like a statue of a commander.
        Everything is beautiful and amazing: the tongue does not turn, there is a count in the spine, on the shoulders the weight of the Egyptian pyramid,
        and in the brains - what\'s in the brains, the devil will already understand.
        Smoke screen. I forget half the material, no synopsises help.</blockquote>

        \tIf the \"skeptic\" turns to politics, then his first thing is characterized by stably strained relations with the press.
        In democratic systems, a politician - a \"skeptic\" - usually escapes from the press as President Reagan did.
        <br><br>

        \t3rd logic is the main consumer of crosswords, logical tasks and tests.
        All this intellectual production is the ideal testing ground on which the 3rd logic can be without interference and risk
        serious traumas to check themselves, to find out how objective is the internal sense of their mental inferiority.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="forth_logic_description"><![CDATA[
         \tWilly-nilly or involuntarily, but about the 4th logic one can get the impression of a function that is knowingly mentally helpless and backward.
         It\'s not like that at all.
         <br><br>

         \tThe essence of the problems of the 4th logic is not the low quality of its functioning,
         but in the fact <i>the owner takes the last place to logic in its internal hierarchy of values. </i>
         <br><br>

         \tOn the example of Pushkin it is easy to see one of the specific features of the 4th logic: the combination of the qualitative work of the logical apparatus
         with complete madness.
         <blockquote>Pushkin was a brilliant polemicist, losing cards to all who knew how to hold them in their hands.</blockquote>

         \tThere is nothing paradoxical about this.
         His polemic gift was opened in the serene atmosphere of a friendly atmosphere.
         While a large card game itself led to discomfort, the tension of the situation, in which,
         according to the laws of the Fourth Functions, <i> Pushkin\'s 4th logic was turned off</i>, and all internal power engineering was focused
         in emotion - <i>the function, which is the first</i> in its internal hierarchy.
         And the result of playing cards, based on emotions, is easy to predict in advance.
         <br><br>

         \tAnd so, depending on the situation, there lives any \"schoolboy\" - clever and foolish in one person.
         4th logic is difficult to give independent mental work, in general, the inclusion of intelligence without immediate and obvious in that need.
         <br><br>

         \tThe brain of a \"schoolboy\" is pragmatic, does not like to look forward and breadth, and quickly molds without pushes from outside.
         In appearance, the 4th logic is almost the same as the second.
         It is also intellectually non-party; easily absorbs, accepts, reproduces, develops any views: dogmatic, dialectical, skeptical…
         <i>The 4th logic is also free and fearless in its assumptions and conclusions, like the 2nd.</i>
         <br><br>

         \tAnd give due, omnivorous, combined with fearlessness is the main and very powerful trump card in the hands of \"schoolboy\".
         Quickly to distinguish 4-th logic from the second allow two things.
         1. The ideology of \"schoolboy\" is completely divorced from his life, and he is not inclined to follow what he himself postulates.
         2. Congenital skepticism.
         <br><br>

         \tHowever, do not confuse it with the active skepticism of the 3rd logic.
         Skepticism of \"schoolboy\" is toothless.
         Pasternak once remarked:
         <blockquote>To be engaged all life intellectual activity all the same, that all life to eat mustard.</blockquote>

         \tThe skepticism of the 4th logic is not a vigorous denial of the effectiveness of the intellectual principle in person, but a mere indifference to it.
         Chekhov, who had 4 logics, wrote:
         <blockquote>I do not have a political, religious and philosophical worldview; I change it monthly…</blockquote>

         \tIn a word, the \"schoolboy\" is energetic only in need, idly curious, internally completely uninhibited, intellectual chameleon.
         And here all its pluses and minuses.
         <br><br>

         \tIn consolation \"schoolboy\" it is necessary to add that he is a champion.
         Among the world\'s population, he is numerically superior to all other logics.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="first_physics_description"><![CDATA[
        \tTall, burly men prevail among the owners of 1st physics.
        They love expensive, catchy fabrics and furs, magnificent, emphasizing already powerful forms, silhouette.
        They do not know the measures in finishing the dress, whether it\'s really expensive or tawdry: a brooch - as big as fist of size, a chain or a ring - as thick as a finger…
        In short we can say that the style of the clothes of the 1st physicist is close to the style of the mafiosi, as they are usually portrayed in the world cinema.
        <br><br>

        \tYou can guess an \"owner\" in a child quite early.
        If in a yard sandbox a child, whose neighbor has dragged a toy, silently, without any preliminary negotiations,
        hits the offender on the ear, then the parents can be congratulated: their child has the 1st physics.
        <br><br>

        \tThe features of bodily plastics are universal: the "owner", if not in a hurry, acts slowly and majestically.
        He, too, can spend hours in the same pose, without experiencing any appreciable inconvenience.
        <br><br>

        \t\"Owner\" is a touch hippopotamus.
        Due to thick-skinnedness, he is physiologically not jealous, and he himself can not be attributed to ideals of fidelity.
        The nature of \"owner\'s\" sexuality is such that he may cheating, as if not cheating.
        <br><br>

        \tAs for the immediate tastes of the 1st Physicist, by virtue of her sensory thick-skinnedness it likes bright colors,
        but it does not distinguish halftones and shades.
        Has a predilection for rough, heavy, spicy food.
        It attracts tart and intense smells.
        <br><br>

        \tThe first physics is usually attributed to the most criminogenic category of citizens.
        This is due to the fact that the first, unconscious impulse in the event of problems provokes the \"owners\" to solve them through illegal actions.
        And not always external and internal brakes are strong enough to overcome this temptation.
        <br><br>

        \t\"Owner\" is a monstrously gambler, and the prospect of instant, effortless enrichment has almost magical power over him.
        Therefore, he is the first victim of all kinds of financial scams, lotteries, gambling, etc.
        Any \"owner\" is a complete materialist, better than anyone who knows his own profit and the value of money.
        <br><br>

        \tNaturally, sports are among the main occupations and interests of the 1st physicist.
        However, the \"owner\" accepts the sport not unconditionally, and not entirely.
        The first function is efficient, therefore 1st physics loves combat sports, with an emphasis not so much on the process of struggle, but on the result.
        Bodybuilding is the closest to the 1st physics: who is more abundant and more revealing will show redundancy
        flesh is extremely appealing to those experiencing the same psychic sensations \"proprietor\".
        <br><br>

        \t\"Owner\" can not be called a \"workaholic\" or a gambler who enjoys work.
        Usually, not taking too much to heart other people's pains and troubles, he, like no one, is acutely experiencing his own property and physical losses.
        Even minor attacks on physics - the backbone of his personality - are often perceived by him as almost the death of the universe.
     ]]></string>

    <string name="second_physics_description"><![CDATA[
        \tThe second physics lives by movement, therefore simplicity, normativity and beauty are just as natural for it as for fish it is natural to breathe in water.
        It is easy to recognise the second physics by the love of purity.
        One has only to enter into a house shining with purity and order, in which it lives by all means.
        <br><br>

        \tCharacteristics which are typical to the second function as such - power, diversity, processivity, dialogue, flexibility - can also be recognized in the second physics.
        \"Toiler\" is the creature who in the physical sense is extremely contact.
        He likes to touch, palm, take care of people and objects, which he considers to be his.

        \tThe second physics is the only true \"workaholic\".
        Labor is needed and dear to it in itself, often regardless of the size of the profit.
        And in matters of transformations, improvements, they do have some special type of thinking.
        <br><br>

        \t2nd physics knows how to love: it is the best lover in the world, if we bear in mind the purely physical meaning of this word.
        In love, the \"toiler\" is indefatigable, confident in himself and in his right to leadership in this field, multifaceted,
        unconventional, resourceful, natural, tolerant, benevolent, responsive, cherishes all its aspects without exception, from the very beginning to the very end.
        <br><br>

        \tThe second physics knows the value of money, knows how and loves to earn it.
        Financial collapse, of course, does not pass for it painlessly, but it is not fatal for it, does not knock out the \"toiler\" from the saddle.
        <br><br>

        \tFrom the point of view of sympathy for political and economic models, the \"laborer\" is best classified as \"social democrats\".
        Violence from selfish motives is generally internally alien to the \"toiler\".
        Therefore, even when, due to circumstances, he takes the path of violence, the \"social-democrat\" does not die in him,
        the \"toiler\" simply transforms into \"Robin Hood\" - a social democrat with a criminal bias, and so as to be reconciled with himself.

     ]]></string>

    <string name="third_physics_description"><![CDATA[
        \tSupersusibility \"touchy\" determines all of its behavioral, legal, economic, aesthetic and other aspects of life.
        If in childhood the 3rd Physics is accompanied by beatings, illnesses, hunger, it often so refines it,
        originally refined, that the physical sensitivity of the \"touchy\" is generally beyond the limits of the generally available and generally understood.
        <br><br>

        \t3rd Physics is very suspicious and with constant attention listens to the work of their own organism, preference is given to prevention, hardening and strengthening the body.
        The main inventors and consumers of yoga, raw food, winter swimming, therapeutic starvation, various kinds of gymnastics, etc. are exactly \"touchy\".
        Fear for oneself and the habit of listening to one\'s own organism, due to the processability of the 3rd physicist, usually turn to others and
        give the world irreconcilable fighters for the purity of nature, active propagandists of a healthy lifestyle and first-class doctors.
        <br><br>

        \t\"Touchy\" is a very marital essence: in search of additional levels of protection, he hurries to marry, trying to cover up his vulnerable body by law.
        The love of the 3rd physicist for children is boundless and sometimes takes excessive forms.
        \"Touchy\", seeing in procreation not just value, but an absolute, independent of time, space and circumstances value,
        it is fecund notoriously and thoughtlessly.
        <br><br>

        \t3rd Physics is jealous in terms of physiological jealousy.
        In light of what has been said about the 3rd Physics, it is not hard to guess that it is unusually law-abiding.
        From the point of view of preferences in socio-economic policy, the third physics is closest to the rank of \"communist\".
        The bottom line is that the "touchy" is the closest thing to the leveling and distribution system.
        The nature of the \"communist\" sympathies of the 3rd physicist is quite clear: it feels itself to be the weakest and most vulnerable element in society.
        <br><br>

        \t\"Touchy\" is a very unimportant fighter, worse than anyone.
        The fact is that, frankly speaking, he is a coward.
        How much the cowardice of the 3rd physicist turns out to be noticeable to outsiders depends on many conditions,
        but the fact that it is less than someone who wants to subject his or her body as a force test is for sure.
        Out of fear, 3rd physicist happens in battle (if it can not be avoided) is too cruel.
        Fear of getting hurt suppresses pity and sense of proportion in it, therefore, as far as the fight goes,
        the excess of necessary self-defense is usual for the 3rd physicist phenomenon.
        However, it is extremely rare to fight \"touchy\".
        Assault and in the home, and in politics for it little acceptable and most unpromising way to solve problems.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="forth_physics_description"><![CDATA[
        \t4th physics is usually pretty with its subtlety and pallor.
        More often \"lazy\" is a slim, thin-boned person, \"asthenic\".
        However, among the 4th physicists there are also people of large, athletic build.
        A remarkable property of the beauty of the 4th physics is also the fact that time is not powerful over it.
        The usual sense of early aging for the 4th physics is, strangely, in contrast to a fresh, healthy appearance.
        <br><br>

        \tSadness is more often than other senses read in the eyes \"lazy\".
        4th physics is born and dies with a sense of the original tragedy of being, with a sense of misfortune.
        Waiting for a catastrophe, bad forebodings are typical for the 4th physics, and the words \"nightmare\", \"sadness\", \"melancholy\" are favorites in her vocabulary.
        <br><br>

        \tThe \"lazy\" one has some mysterious connection with the moon.
        As the moon shines weak, only reflected light, and \"lazy\", according to the law of the Fourth Functions, is only a reflection of higher, autonomous physical energetics.
        <br><br>

        \tThe term \"lazy\" reflects not so much the manner of behavior, but as the psychological orientation of the individual.
        On the contrary, apparently the 4th physics often looks like a hard worker.
        It is plodding, unpretentious, fearless in wasting its strength, and it is executive within the limits of her allotted.
        <br><br>

        \tSensation of the weakenedness of the physics sphere lives in \"lazy\" people since birth, however, it does not bother him much.
        \"Lazy\" is the creature who is absolutely fearless.
        The reckless bravery of the 4th physicist looks from the side a remarkable dignity, but in fact is not so.
        The fourth function, that is, then the least you value, the feat is not great.
        In addition, as with every virtue, courage \"lazy\" has its downside: not sparing himself, he is not inclined to spare others.
        <br><br>

        \tAsceticism is the economic program of the 4th physics.
        \"Lazy\" can live with minimum of comfort without much stress, but it does not follow from this that he is oppressed by luxury.
        He is too indifferent to the physical layer of life to take seriously the problem of the personal level of consumption.
        <br><br>

        \tFor example, Einstein, having provided for himself for old age the most elementary prosperity,
        could use a check for $15,000 from the Rockefeller Foundation as a book bookmark.
        The \"Lazy\" is a win-win politician.
        Being a brave person, he does not risk breaking his neck on what the policy of the neck usually breaks: money and women.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="first_will_description"><![CDATA[
        \tThe first will is a born leader: for it to manage people is as easily and naturally as breathing.
        It is born with a two-layer picture of the universe: there is a top and a bottom.
        The premonition of the 1st will to be the chosen one is its program, character, image and meaning of its life.
        <br><br>

        \tBelonging to the highest of the two worlds makes some adjustments to the representation on the rules of law and ethics of the 1st will.
        \"King\" in any case can not be called an immoral creature, he honors the law and does not like to violate the norms prevailing in society,
        but some duality associated with the two-stage picture of the universe, in ethics and law of the 1st will does exist.
        <br><br>

        \tUnconditional compliance with all the rules, in its opinion, is necessary for beings belonging to the second, the lower world.
        As for the beings of the upper world, for them the rule of law and morality must be observed, but not unconditionally.
        <br><br>

        \tThe first will refers to the surrounding smoothly, with no distinction between ranks and titles.
        Formally, the 1st will is a supporter of equality.
        But equality of a kind, where not all have equal rights, and injustice in front of it.
        <br><br>

        \tLife of the \"King\" is tragic from the beginning.
        The trouble is that the 1st will allows the functions below to be implemented only in \"royal\", hierarchically elevated forms.
        Another tragic motive of life of the \"King\" is contained in his voluntarist slogan:
        <blockquote>If you want, you will succeed!</blockquote>

        \tThe tragedy here lies in the very unrealistic slogan, the deliberate refusal to compromise with the environment, nature, the world, society, other people's will and desires.
        \"If you want, you will succeed!\" – the 1st will shouts, pissing against the wind, but the spray does not fly at all where the will wants, but where the wind blows.
        <br><br>

        \tNothing invigorates the 1st the will as authority.
        1st will loves the power, with a pure, devoid of impurities love.
        Power for it is not a means of achieving wealth or realizing old ideas, but a goal valuable in itself.
        Of course, the death of a career or a perceived lack of prospects, for the 1st will be tragic.
        <br><br>

        \tThe first Will is born leader.
        But maybe even more than confident in their right to power, born \"King\", confident in their right to disobedience.
        <br><br>

        \tUncontrollability is the earliest sign of the 1st will.
         \"Kings\" children are the most stubborn, the most difficult children in the world.
        It is almost impossible to agree with them, violence does not work, tears are useless.
        <br><br>

        \t\"King\" is an amazing creature, he never relaxes.
        <i>His self-control is absolute.</i>
        Like a knight, clad in the armor of his iron will, \"King\" passes through life, alien to passions, temptations, weaknesses, attachments.
        1st will create an extremely solid, made of a single stone, and a person deeply lonely.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="second_will_description"><![CDATA[
        \tThe rejection of dictatorship, the desire for full-fledged dialogue when making decisions - this is procession of the 2nd will.
        The embodiment of the same \"nobility\ "is the so-called \"delegation of responsibility\".
        Alien to the craving for petty guardianship, the 2nd will, without removing the responsibility from itself, seeks to share it with all participants,
        giving them complete freedom of forms of implementation.
        <br><br>

        \tIn a letter Goethe reported:
        <blockquote>I'm busy raising my grandson.
        It is that I allow him to do resolutely whatever he pleases, and I hope in this way to form him before,
        than my parents will be here.</blockquote>

        \t<i>Internal freedom and the ability to free others are the true norm of the second Will.</i>
        <br><br>

        \t\"Nobleman\" - the darling of destiny.
        The basis of the human psyche - the will - takes in its order of functions the best, the second line and thus provides
        the holder of the 2nd will, unknown to others, peace of mind.
        The strength and flexibility of the 2nd will give a person of rare integrity and courage for life.
        <br><br>

        \t\"Nobleman\" has a big heart.
        2nd will is able to truly love, because genuine love is commitment.
        <br><br>

        \tThe simplicity and openness of the 2nd Will is not always to its benefit.
        First, dishonest people sometimes use these spiritual properties.
        And secondly, it creates a well-deserved image of the creature, rather naive, primitive, limited,
        who very easily can understand people. Which is true, growing out of the heroic spiritual health of a \"Nobleman \" and ordinary human egocentrism
        which is interpreting the whole world to its sample.
        <br><br>

        \t2nd Will is fearless in relationships with people.
        Those who are trying to experiment with the character of a \"Nobleman\" and try to taste it, simply forget the fairly banal truth: only very strong people can afford weakness.
        <br><br>

        \tFlattering a \"Nobleman\" is as useless as humiliating, but they have a great sense of self-esteem and independence.
        The attitude of the 2nd Will to glory is also better to be conveyed by one short quote from Pasternak:
        <blockquote>It is ugly to be famous.</blockquote>

        \tBy and large, \"Nobleman\" is eager not for fame, but for complete self-realization.
        <br><br>

        \tThe first external sign of the 2nd will, like the will of all, is the look.
        The look of \"Nobleman\" is benevolent and somewhat distracted.
        It seems to say:
        <blockquote>Everything is calm, I am glad to meet you, but if you want, I will not insist on continuing it.</blockquote>
    ]]></string>

    <string name="third_will_description"><![CDATA[
         \tTotal vulnerability is a distinctive and most frightening trait of the psyche \"Bourgeois\".
         Being unable to protect herself, he often condemns himself to hidden anger, aggressiveness, secrecy and loneliness.
         <br><br>

         \tReally, the term \"complex\" only applies the mind of \"Bourgeois\" as it really is a whole range of ills,
         burns and ulcers, threatening to grow into one multifunctional festering wound.
         Therefore, means of self-defense of 3rd will have a complete universal set.
         <br><br>

         \tEvery Third function has its \"fig leaf\".
         The 3rd will also has it - this is hypocrisy.
         But since the entire order of functions of \"Bourgeois\" is vulnerable, he has to cover himself entirely,
         all of the existing pigeon leaf figs: now idiot, now hypocritically, now ironically, now falling into the deepest skepticism.
         <br><br>

         \tLying is the earliest and surest sign of the 3rd will.
         It lies often, automatically, impulsively, stupidly, senselessly.
         A lie for the \"bourgeois\" is a universal tool of self-defense and self-affirmation and therefore is exposed at the first imaginary or real threat,
         as well as at the first opportunity to splurge.
         <br><br>

         \tPretense, and more directly to say, hypocrisy, is an integral part of the same tendency of the 3rd will to lie.
         The 3rd will is a born actor of the theater, which is better called not \"social\", but \"hierarchical\", because \"Bourgeois\"
         acting not only in society, but also in the family.
         <br><br>

         \t\"Bourgeois\" is a natural double agent, because he does not have enough spirit to oppose or belong to something,
         will - and this is the only and main reason for his paradoxical duality of personality.
         <br><br>

         \tIt is impossible to describe everything that, in the eyes of \"Bourgeois\", is important in determining a place in life:
         place on the space ladder, place on the ladder of nature, age, gender, race, nationality, religion, origin,
         position, appearance, property status, profession, education and many other seemingly inconspicuous items,
         allowing \"bourgeois\" to find each a special place in his caste picture of the world.
         <br><br>

         \t3rd will loves and hates power.
         It envies, hates and at the same time unconsciously and almost disinterestedly clings to the power, strives to stay longer in its field.
         3rd will basically does not recognize their mistakes.
         It loves titles, diplomas and awards.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="forth_will_description"><![CDATA[
        \t\"Serfs\" are the cutest people in the world.
        It is easy to breathe in their field, as if in any other, their field can be passed through.
        You can even enter there in a tank - there will be no resistance.
        Because it is so easy to breathe in the field \"serf\" - it is discharged.
        <br><br>

        \tThe picture of the universe, living in the soul of the 4th will, practically repeats the corresponding picture of the 1st will:
        the whole world is a hierarchy consisting of two levels: upper and lower.
        The difference is that \"Serf\" automatically places itself not on the top, as \"King\", but on its lower degree,
        <i>taking the role of a flock.</i>
        From here, one of the 4th will be its untimely childishness.
        <br><br>

        \tLimitless frankness is the achilles heel of \"Serf\".
        Low self-esteem is an incomparable, priceless gift.
        It makes life of \"Serf\" light, cloudless, and the psyche is so stable that even time is not powerful over the 4th will.
        <br><br>

        \tThe family is the first of the public cells, which \"serf \" once and for all entrusts its will.
        Age, position in society does not affect his place in the family, he feels like a child until the end of his days
        and not even trying to eventually become equal with them.

        <blockquote>Two friends, men who have already managed to live and turn gray, to this day hide their addiction to tobacco from their parents,
        as if nothing had changed since that happy childish time when they could be punished for cigarettes found in their pockets.</blockquote>

        \tNext is the school, where \"Serf\" stands out exemplary of their behavior.
        <br><br>

        \tThe 4th will is the most faithful spouse, the loyal subordinate.
        But the paradox, namely, \"serf\" often looks like a terrible rebel and oppositionist.
        For example, \"soft as wax\", Bukharin was considered almost chronic and almost official head of the opposition to Lenin.
        Molotov was the only one who openly argued with Stalin, and this despite the fact that both had the 4th will.
        <br><br>

        \t\"Serf\" is not the master of himself, rock and inertia rule the whole fate.
        In addition to simplicity, openness, and selflessness, the 4th will is characterized by a sincere unwillingness to take on serious responsibility.
        <br><br>

        \tThe 4th will itself is unspeakably surprised to be at the top of a public pyramid or some serious structure.
        Darwin quite sincerely wrote:
        <blockquote>It is truly amazing that a person of such modest abilities as I could in a number of
        significant issues have a significant impact on the views of people of science. </blockquote>
    ]]></string>

    <string name="first_function_description"><![CDATA[
        \tThis is the most important, strong and typical side of our nature, our most important weapon of survival.
        <i>Support personality, the foundation of the psyche.</i>
        <i>Always on display.</i>
        <i>Formulates a personal goal in life, the meaning of life, the value system, we look at the world first of all through the prism of the 1st function.</i>
        <br><br>

        \tThis is our main weapon in conflicts: family, workers - any.
        Always turns on first (first reaction).
        With any danger, if a person has the first function:
        <i>physics</i>, then he either hits hard or runs away quickly;
        <i>logics</i>, then he immediately interprets the situation and finds a solution;
        <i>emotion</i>, then he begins to gush and scream so that the enemies themselves will scatter.
        <br><br>

        \tIn addition, we need weapons not only to fight the enemies.
        For example, there are weapons which we may use in our love tasks, when you need to continue your kind.
        This is also the task of survival, which is given to us by nature and which each 1st function solves in its own way:
        <i>1st logic</i> try to hit your mind;
        <i>1st physics</i> will demonstrate its appearance - beauty, strength, pumped muscles, material wealth;
        <i>1st emotion</i>will sing serenades and read poems;
        <i>1st will</i> just take his hand and say: \"Come with me!\"
        <br><br>

        \tThe first function is very strong, but it has one problem. <b> It is redundant and gross. </b>
        <i>1-emotional</i> a person is prone to tantrums on any occasion.
        <i>1-logical</i> person - frank bore. He is not able to hear another point of view, if it does not coincide with his own.
        <i>1-physical</i> person is greedy and aggressive. So among the thieves and gangsters there are many 1-physical people.
        He is also prone to gluttony and many other pleasant things that physics gives.
        <i>1-will</i> a person rudely puts pressure on everyone else, breaks them on the knee, demands that everything be according to his will and not listen to anyone but himself.
        <br><br>

        \tThe first function is a sledgehammer.
        This is not a very thin instrument, the most suitable for punching walls.
        But this is not an hour-long screwdriver for repairing fine mechanisms.
     ]]></string>

    <string name="second_function_description"><![CDATA[
        \tThe ideal function in our psycho-type is the best and most healthy part of human nature.
        <i>It does not set goals in life, but it is the main tool for achieving them.</i>
        <i>Is not conspicuous neither themselves nor others.</i>
        <i>Is process-centric</i> and, unlike the first function, it is able to listen to others and communicate with them.
        It is smooth such what should be ideally — it not too much and not too little.
        <br><br>

        \tFor example, the best actor is a person not with the first emotion, but with the second.
        When necessary, he can cry or laugh, and it can take only 2 seconds of your time between these events.
        <br><br>

        \tThe most logical person is one with the second logic, not with the first because, that the first usually thinks so:
        <blockquote>I'm the smartest here. Therefore, either listen to what I am telling you, or are to blame.</blockquote>
        \tAnd the second logic will say:
        <blockquote>It is interesting and your opinion to listen, let's discuss!</blockquote>

        \tThe second will is a person whom it is difficult to break, bend, but at the same time he does not put pressure on other people.
        The second physics is the most industrious, energetic and viable people.
        <br><br>

        \tThe 2nd function is a river that, like the Volga, flows endlessly and for a long time, and you always know that the water will not end in it.
        So is our 2nd function.
        It is like good health - we don’t notice it at all because we believe that it is inexhaustible until some kind of problem happens.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="third_function_description"><![CDATA[
        \tAs you understand, we must be unlucky about something - all people have not only advantages, but also disadvantages.
        More precisely, we have what we consider to be our shortcomings, about which we have been thinking from childhood that we have not been very successful in this.
        <br><br>

        \tWe look at other people, and we see that they have developed this coolly, but we do not have it.
        And we begin to either envy them, or fall in love with them, or learn from them, etc.
        This is the third function:
        <i>The root of our self-doubt;</i>
        <i>The main reason for our inferiority complexes, insults, conflicts.</i>
        <i>The source of love and hate, discomfort, feelings of lack of realization.</i><br><br>

        \tIf a person has 3rd logic, he is not sure that he is smart and competent enough.
        If a person has the 3rd emotion, he is not sure that he is relaxed enough, opened, not clamped, etc.
        If a person has the 3rd will, he is always afraid that he is not respected and valued enough.
        If a person has a 3rd physics, he is not sure of his beauty, masculinity, and that he is sufficiently provided.
        A girl constantly doubts whether she is beautiful, whether her men want her. Men similarly doubt about the opinion of girls about themselves.
        <br><br>

        \tWe are always afraid of hitting the 3rd function:
        3rd logic afraid of accusations of stupidity,
        3rd physics-physical violence,
        3rd will — humiliation,
        3rd emotion-hysterical.
        <br><br>

        \tThis translates into very different things.
        The fact is that <i> the third function is the same process-oriented as the second one.</i>
        The process of the third means that a person must constantly prove that he has everything in order.
        The first and fourth functions are effective-/"I proved to myself, and everything is fine/".
        <br><br>

        \tSince we have this most painful place, we always try to cover it, as the players cover their most sensitive place during the wall.
        And we constantly go, having covered with a fig leaf our third function.
        It is said that the lower functions (3-4) are conditionally weak, but in fact only the fourth function is weak.
        The third is very strong because it is the <i> driver and the engine of our self-development.</i>
        <br><br>

        \tFor example, who often goes to the gym or engaged in extreme sports,
        tortures themselves on curiously biathlon, triathlon and other marathons? 3-physical people!
        Who are the most beautiful and sophisticated girls? 3-physical!
        2-physical are sure in their beauty, they knows, that with it all in order.
        A 3-physical will prove it all my life.
        Who reads and learns the most? 3-logical!
        Who is the most refined musician? 3-emotional!
        <br><br>

        <blockquote>Compare the music of Tom York from Radiohead (3 emotion) and Freddie Mercury (1 emotion).
        Whose music is more elegant?</blockquote>

        \tBy the way, who are the coolest managers? 3-will ones.
        They are flexible, not confident, but carefully hide it — so a lot of work on themselves.
        They are also great manipulators because they understand people much better and thinner than others.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="forth_function_description"><![CDATA[
       \tEach of us has this function, but <i>it is not important to us.</i>
       For example, ask a person:
       <blockquote><b>-What is your favorite music?</b><br>
       -Different! I love various music!</blockquote>

       \tHe has 4th emotion - he will listen to what they give.
       The fourth function is a kickshaw. We use it, of course, but when necessary.
       <br><br>

       \tThere is 4th logic, and brains work normally.
       A person with 4th physics has a body, right? So there is physics.
       And the 4th emotion exists.
       But it doesn’t seem to matter - we don’t steam ourselves and don\'t get much pleasure from it - so we don’t develop this function.
       <br><br>

       \tInterestingly, in extreme conditions, the 4th function is disabled.
       That is, a person with a 4th physicist in a crisis situation will simply have his legs taken away and he will not be able to move.
       The person with the 4th logic will stop thinking altogether.
       <br><br>

       \tBy the way, it's very good for the soldiers to have the 4th emotion because in extreme situations they do not lose their temper.
       Alexander of Macedon or Napoleon rushed into battle completely without fear, their emotions turned off.
       This is both good and bad, depending on the situation.
    ]]></string>
</resources>