<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="introduction_title">Psychosophy is</string>
    <string name="introduction_psychosophy_definition"><![CDATA[
    \tA humanistic worldview on relations between people, based on the psychical typology of A. Yu. Afanasyev.
    It also studies the person\'s priorities, his own ideas about his inner world and his capabilities.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="introduction_psychosophy_definition_bases"><![CDATA[
    \tIt has 4 bases: <i> Will, Logic, Emotion, Physics. </i>
    From a philosophical point of view, they correspond to: <i> Spirit, Mind, Soul and Body. </i>
    ]]></string>

    <string name="introduction_psychosophy_bases">
    \tEach base of typology occupies a certain step in the hierarchy of the psychic type,
         which affects the values and behavior of a person.
    </string>
    <string name="introduction_psychosophy_bases_and_functions">About the bases and functions</string>

    <string name="introduction_psychosophy_personalities"><![CDATA[
    \tThe personality psychotype (according to Afanasyev) is denoted by the first letters of the name of the grounds,
    beginning with the first (most expressed in behavior and values) and up to the fourth.
    In total, there are 24 possible personality psychotypes.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="introduction_psychosophy_pseudonyms"><![CDATA[
    \tIn addition, there are type aliases. For example, the type with the order of the bases \"Will, Logic, Emotion, Physics\" is denoted by WLEF and has a pseudonym \"Socrates\".
    ]]></string>

    <string name="introduction_psychosophy_psychotypes_button">All psychotypes</string>
    <string name="introduction_psychosophy_my_psychotype_button">Find your type</string>

    <string name="introduction_psychosophy_relationships"><![CDATA[
        \tDifferent variants of relations between representatives of different types are possible.
        Their complementarity depends on the position of one or another reason in the structure of each type of priorities.
    ]]></string>
    <string name="introduction_psychosophy_relationships_button">About relationships</string>
</resources>