<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="LEPW_title">LEFW - Augustine</string>

    <string name="LEPW_short"><![CDATA[
    \tIn the soul and in the life of \"Augustine\" - the inventor, researcher, systematizer.
    \tHe is interested in the results of scientific research.
    He subtly feels the physical condition of loved ones, cares about the welfare of himself and family members, animals.
    <br><br>
    \tHe is an unsure person, but in an extreme situation, he acts decisively.<br>
    It is more convenient for him to be led, he is peaceful and benevolent.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="LEPW_full"><![CDATA[
    \tThe man, the carrier of this type - <i> thoughtful, balanced, delicate, peaceful, reasonable</i>.
    Tends to the logical and philosophical understanding of the world.
    <br><br>

    <i>\tThe thirst for intellectual knowledge </i> is one of the main features of his character, and he pays special attention to learning everything new.
    Its internal attitude is:

    <blockquote>- The world is systemic. <br>
    - Thought can explain a lot. <br>
    - The world is open to exploration. <br>
    - Everything is predetermined and not accidental, there is a deeper meaning in everything, mediated by cause-and-effect relationships.<br>
    - The material world is imperfect and needs to be transformed endlessly for comfort and convenience, and I know how to make it more perfect.<br>
    - There is something wrong with my health and appearance.<br>
    - The well-being of the family and offspring are my main values.</blockquote>

    \tGetting older, people like \"Augustine\" become interested in various philosophical and mathematical models of the world order, psychology, mythology,
    philosophy in all its diversity. However, they often have their own strong opinion, and it is difficult to convince them.
    In the case of a high intellectual level of development of his personality and the presence of educational baggage, he comfortably feels himself in science,
    first of all, theoretical.
    <br><br>

    \t\"Augustine\" has an excellent memory, excellent erudition, deep, solid knowledge on certain issues, acquired in the process of self-education.
    His character manifests itself in a <i>flexible form of communication, a critical analysis of the surrounding reality</i>, based on his own ideas;
    <i>propensity to dogmatism</i>, peremptory and unconditional self-righteousness; promoting their ideas and attitudes.
    <br><br>

    \tIn everyday communication, such a person is an excellent interlocutor, quite emotional and pleasant.
    It is characterized by a subtle sense of humor, an original sense of beauty, an interest in complex and unusual art,
    for example, cinema, graphics, folklore, oriental dance, some spiritual practices.
    He is artistic, emotionally relaxed, his emotions are free and adequate to the moment of intercourse, and he always knows how to say what he needs.
    <br><br>

    \tSometimes sadness visits him because of the feeling of his ordinary human weakness in the face of objective difficulties,
    generated by the surrounding material world, as well as by virtue of feeling \"white crow\" among people.
    <br><br>

    \tA man like \"Augustine\" <i> feels fine the physical condition of friends and relatives </i>, selflessly cares about them.
    Despite his suspiciousness, he is engaged in prevention and is leaning towards a healthy lifestyle.
    It is very difficult for him to eradicate his bad habits (if any): his willpower is weak.
    <br><br>

    \tHe carefully hides his external physiological defects.
    <i>He feels duality and insecurity in relations with the world of material things </i> - everything that relates to the body, appearance, fashion,
    nutrition, carnal pleasures.
    He fears more than other physical abuse and beatings.
    He equips his permanent and even temporary dwelling with joy and special meaning.
    He works to exhaustion, not knowing the measure.
    <br><br>

    \tMoney is very important to him.
    If they are not enough, it strives for a minimum (if only it is guaranteed) and is content with small things, hoping to earn money for the quality life of their family.
    According to his actions, he is lecherous, but selective and cowardly, unpredictable in sensations, clean and squeamish at the same time,
    and at the same time risks changing partners and preferences.
    <br><br>

    \tHe is a man who is not self-assured in everyday life, is peace-loving, benevolent, avoiding conflicts in all areas of life, except intellectual disputes.
    In rare disputes and discussions, hidden, sometimes powerful intellectual cynicism, globality and systematic thinking, accuracy as the quality of his mentality make themselves felt.
    He is interested in promoting his ideas, would like to meet a like-minded person with pronounced strong-willed character traits.
    <br><br>

    \t\"Augustine\" is more convenient to be led, subordinate, sacrificial in everyday affairs and events. He believes in Destiny.
    In an extreme situation, it can act decisively and surprise everyone (including himself) with heroism, courage, physical and mental endurance, intellectual power.
    Able to record and win in sports.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="ELWP_title"> ELWP – Andersen </string>

    <string name="ELWP_short"><![CDATA[
    \t\"Andersen\" - capable and, most likely, a talented person.
    He dreams of a career, of recognition, of fame, however, his deeds and actions are half-hearted, and he often does not achieve his goals.
    This is from self-doubt.
    <br><br>

    \tSometimes he deceives himself and others - this is his proven tool for self-defense.
    He is a complex person, he often becomes irritated, angry, offended by the whole world, including himself!
    He often creates discomfort in communicating with other people, sometimes in open conflict.
    <br><br>

    \tIn everyday life, he is not selective, content with small. He is healthy, fearless and prone to risk.
    He is very emotional, romantic with elements of tragedy, prone to frequent depressions, and his mood often changes dramatically.
    He likes to talk, but rarely listens to the opinions of others and more often does not trust others.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="ELWP_full"><![CDATA[
    \tThe person who bears this mental type is <i> passionate, gifted, capable, and often talented.</i>
    He loves to create, and creativity is present in his life literally in all his activities.
    <br><br>

    \tHe is emotional, romantic, unbalanced, with a sense of the tragedy of being.
    Mood often changes dramatically, he does not know moderation in anything.
    Love, hate, intellectual delight, disgust, anger, disbelief in one\'s own strength, guilt, fun - all passion absorbs,
    and at such a moment nothing can serve as a deterrent.
    <br><br>

    \tMany carriers of \"Andersen\" type are distinguished by an excessive emotional and somewhat lingering reaction to events.
    Such people are very vulnerable.
    The pervasive theme of their thinking is regret that the world is getting worse.
    All their lives for themselves, they are too attentive observers and harsh judges!
    <br><br>

    \tSuch a person has excellent logical and literary abilities at the same time, an excellent memory for details.
    He is talkative and witty, ready and attentively listen to the interlocutor.
    His opinion rarely depends on someone else\'s opinion, and more often he does not trust other people with him.
    <br><br>

    \tIt is characterized by a philosophical turn of mind.
    There are a lot of carriers of this type in the underground (amateur creative and intellectual communities such as, for example, fiction clubs),
    where there is room for the development of their concepts - very non-standard ones, but those that can not always be recognized by society as serious,
    really scientific.
    Such theoretical constructions constitute one of the main pleasures of their lives.
    <br><br>

    \tA man like \"Andersen\" is internally deeply unsure of himself.
    This basic contradiction he carefully hides from others.
    Himself is hardly recognized in a certain duality of attitude, ill-will towards people who, as it seems to him,
    they do not understand him - an extraordinary and talented person.
    <br><br>

    \tPascal wrote:
    <blockquote>A man is by nature trusting, distrustful, timid, courageous…<br>
    Dependent and eager for independence in a state of impermanence, longing, anxiety</blockquote>

    \tHe often sleeps badly at night, dreaming of moving up the career ladder, of recognition and fame,
    but all his actions are often half-hearted, and he does not achieve his goals.
    This is from internal insecurity.
    <br><br>

    \tHe often deceives himself and others - it is a proven tool for self-defense.
    He creates discomfort in communicating with other people without noticing it, and sometimes openly conflicts.
    He is a difficult person, it is difficult for him, therefore he is often irritated, angry, offended by the whole world, including himself!
    In his heart, he remains a vulnerable teenager who needs a kind and wise parent.
    <br><br>

    \t<i>Making decisions, forcing oneself to be active is difficult for him.</i>
    For example, there are cases when students of the psychotype \"Andersen\", knowing the material well, did not dare to take the exam because
    that they were not confident in their abilities to gather at the right moment.
    This explains their pessimism, which is realized in the conclusion that the world is getting worse.
    <br><br>

    \tMaterial values, money, carnal pleasures for a carrier like \"Andersen\" are of little (as if of secondary importance) -
    usually by virtue of preoccupation with philosophical reflections and creativity.
    Sometimes the material world is perceived not just as a burden, but as something that should either change (therefore it cannot represent global values),
    or as something to donate without much regret.
    <br><br>

    \tIn everyday life, \"Andersen\" is often not selective, content with little.
    The room has a chronic mess.
    Easily adopts the option of life, style, preferences and tastes of his companion for life.
    <br><br>

    \tLeans towards vegetarianism, special diets, separate meals, oriental health practices.
    Many \"Anderson\" addicted to the culture of the East, traveling to places of power, tend to visit India, Tibet, etc.
    <br><br>

    \tThey are healthy, fearless and prone to risk.
    Outwardly very attractive with subtlety (iconography) features, slim figure (if there are no hormonal disruptions in the body).
    <br><br>

    \tCarriers of ELWF type usually believe in fate and their special purpose in this world.
    <br><br>

    \tBy profession, they are more often theater actors, artists, designers, writers, poets, musicians, travelers who dream of power, fame and recognition.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="PLWE_title"> PLWE – Aristippus </string>

    <string name="PLWE_short"><![CDATA[
    \t\"Aristippus\" is a holiday person.
    Pleasure, material well-being for him is more important than spiritual and social values.
    He is often lazy, although in everyday life he prefers to do the main thing himself.
    <br><br>

    \tIn dealing with people, he is the best, but little emotional interlocutor.
    He is a capable and, most likely, talented person.
    He dreams of a career, recognition, fame, but his deeds and actions are half-hearted, and he often fails to achieve his goals.
    This is from self-doubt.
    <br><br>

    \tHe often deceives himself and others - this is his proven tool for self-defense.
    He is a difficult person, often irritated, angry, offended by the whole world, including himself!
    Sometimes he openly conflicts with other people.
    <br><br>

    \tHe likes to talk and impose his ideas on others.
    He rarely listens to someone else's opinion and does not trust others.
    He is a restaurateur, a realtor, a show business manager, a politician in his heart and vocation.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="PLWE_full"><![CDATA[
    \tThe carrier of this mental type is a rare erudite, a most interesting interlocutor and lecturer, an unbalanced, gifted, capable and, most likely, talented person.
    <br><br>

    \tA person like \"Aristippus\" is often called \"holiday person\".
    Pleasures, carnal pleasures, material well-being for him are more important than spiritual values.
    But most important of all is social status as an instrument of hoarding.
    <br><br>

    \tInternal attitude is:
    <blockquote>- Money rules the world, a lot of money does not happen <br>
    - Happiness - in the amount of money and material objects owned.<br>
    - Career and position - a tool for increasing wealth.</blockquote>

    \tFeatures of manifestation in behavior and character:
    <blockquote>- The tendency for hoarding and luxury, frills food.<br>
    - The need to satisfy carnal pleasures.<br>
    - Tendency to take bribes.<br>
    - Tightness, laziness, lethargy, \"thick skin\", idleness.<br>
    - Thoroughness in places of permanent residence.<br>
    - The desire to own real estate, expensive cars, jewelry, good clothes, shoes and more.</blockquote>

    \tIn ordinary conversation, a great conversationalist, chatty, a little emotional, but fascinating.
    It is characterized by a sense of humor, satire and sarcasm.
    He's an emotionally uninhibited man.
    His emotions are free and adequate to the moment of communication, and he always knows how to say what you need.
    He is a good speaker and is interested in a variety of issues and concerns.
    <br><br>

    \tA person like PLWE is inwardly deeply unsure of himself.
    This is the basic contradiction he carefully hides from others.
    Himself hardly admits of a certain ambivalence of attitude, unkindness to the people.
    He falls asleep, dreaming of moving up the career ladder, recognition, fame and wealth.
    But more often he does not keep this word, his actions are half-hearted, and he does not achieve his goals.
    It comes from inner uncertainty.
    In the soul \"Aristippus\" remains vulnerable teenager who needs a good and wise \"parents\".
    <br><br>

    \tBy vocation carriers of the \"Aristippus\" type are lawyers, realtors, politicians, lawyers, Directors of shops, warehouses, various funds, centers and other organizations.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="WELP_title"> WELP – Akhmatova </string>

    <string name="WELP_short"><![CDATA[
     \t\"Akhmatova\" – a born leader and knows that her decisions will be implemented.
     She is ambitious and dreams of a good career.
     In communicating with people, she is the best interlocutor and actively influences and influences through emotional domination.
     Her emotions are free and adequate to the moment of communication.
     She\'s a born actor.
     <br><br>

     \t\"Akhmatova's\" speech is verbose and it is not easy to speak in public.
     In everyday life, it is not selective, content with little.
     <br><br>

     \tShe is fearless and prone to risk.
     She is a complex person with a pronounced dark-colored attitude.
     She is a film actor, a politician, a bright speaker, a director, a leader with a dictatorial style of management.
   ]]> </string>

    <string name="WELP_full"><![CDATA[
    \tA person of this type is a born leader and performs decisions by 90-100%.
    He is ambitious, dreams of a good career, goes ahead, he can handle the career of a tough leader.
    <br><br>

    \tIts internal attitude is:
    <blockquote>-Claim to primacy and power.<br>
    - Domination and total control.<br>
    - Fear of public speaking.<br>
    - Acting as an instrument of influence and influence on the crowd.</blockquote>

    \tFeatures of internal attitude\'s manifestation in behavior and character:
    <blockquote>- Purpose. <br>
    - Jealousy, ingratitude, callousness.<br>
    - Ambition, selfishness.<br>
    - Disregard for the competitors.<br>
    - High self-esteem.<br>
    - Arrogance, the requirement of worship.<br>
    - Deviation from social norms.<br>
    - Focus on their own lack of understanding.<br>
    - Caution in conclusions, a permanent dispute with no result. <br>
    - Tendency to ask clarifying questions.<br>
    - Verbosity, pauses in conversation.<br>
    - The use of words-parasites, interjections.<br>
    - Logical \"brake\" in class or group.<br>
    - Instead of a simple solution, it offers several complex.<br>
    - Passion to mental activities and hidden revolt against it.<br>
    - The complexity of the thinking process. </blockquote>

    \tIn normal communication, the person, the carrier of the type \"Akhmatova\" - the original interlocutor, quite emotional and wordy.
    His speech is bright, interesting, incendiary, he has a good sense of humor.
    He is artistic, emotionally relaxed, his emotions are free and adequate to the moment of intercourse, but he does not always know how to say what he needs.
    Sometimes they jokingly call it chatterbox.
    <br><br>

    \tHe feels insecure in the logical sphere, in interviews, discussions, laconic formulations, in the choice of one of several possible solutions.
    It is not easy for him to perform in public.
    It is important for him to have in his environment consultants, experts, whose advice can be relied upon.
    <br><br>

    \tMaterial values, money, carnal pleasures for a carrier of the type VELF have a small (as if secondary) value.
    Sometimes the material world is perceived not just as a burden, but as something that should either change (therefore it cannot represent global value),
    or as something to donate without much regret.
    <br><br>

    \tIn everyday life, he is often not selective, content with small.
    The place of residence is a chronic mess.
    Easily adopts the option of life, style, preferences and tastes of his companion for life.
    <br><br>

    \tTends to vegetarianism, special diets, separate nutrition.
    Many \"Akhmatova\" addicted to the culture of the East, travel to places of Power, become hermits.
    Carriers such as \"Akhmatova\" usually believe in destiny and their special purpose in this world.
    <br><br>

    \tThey are healthy, fearless and prone to risk.
    Externally, they are attracted by subtlety (iconography) of features, slim figure (if there are no hormonal disruptions in the body).
    <br><br>

    \tBy profession, as a rule - politicians, directors, actors, writers, poets, travelers, athletes who dream of power, fame and recognition.
    ]]></string>


    <string name="LPEW_title"> LPEW – Berthier </string>

    <string name="LPEW_short"><![CDATA[
    \tIn the soul and in life \"Berthier\" - the inventor, researcher.
    He is interested in the results of scientific research.
    He is a healthy and enduring person, perhaps a workaholic, a good caring parent, his house is in order and prosperity.
    <br><br>

    \tHe appears as an unemotional person, but alone with himself he sets free his feelings and experiences.
    He is an unsure person, but in an extreme situation, he acts decisively.
    It is more convenient for him to be led.
    <br><br>

    \tHe is peaceful and benevolent.
    By vocation and soul, he is a consultant in various fields of activity and a kind person, a teacher and a family man of one love.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="LPEW_full"><![CDATA[
    \tA man of this type - thoughtful, very hardworking, unemotional, delicate, peaceful, sensible,
    prone to logical and philosophical understanding of the world.
    The thirst for intellectual knowledge is one of the main features of his character, and he pays special attention to the knowledge of everything new and systemic.
    He is a good consultant and strategist, artisan and master.
    <br><br>

    \His internal attitude is:
    <blockquote>- The world is systemic.<br>
    - Thought can explain a lot. <br>
    - The world is open to exploration. <br>
    - Everything is predetermined and not accidental, there is a deeper meaning in everything, mediated by cause-and-effect relationships.<br>
    - Dispassion and stability in the expression of emotions is a lifestyle.<br>
    - Display of strong feelings and emotions is unacceptable,
    an open experience in people of deeply seething inside mental states (love, hate, delight, disappointment, etc.)</blockquote>

    \tCharacteristics of the behavior and character:
    <blockquote>- Emotional dryness (constrained laughter, nervous tears).<br>
    - Inadequacy in emotional manifestations.<br>
    - The presence of the only (as a rule) object of passion and love.<br>
    - \"Glassy\" stare.<br>
    - Exhausting control of the emotional state of a meaningful environment.<br>
    - Very deeply hidden feelings.<br>
    - Traction to art.<br>
    - Secret activities and tests themselves in poetry, literature, music, painting, theater, etc.</blockquote>

    \tDifferent types of philosophical and mathematical models of the world order, typology, psychology,
    philosophy in all their diversity are also interesting to the bearer of the type "Bertier".
    On many topics, he has his own firm opinion.
    In the case of a high intellectual level of personal development and the presence of educational baggage,
    the carrier of the type \"Berthier\" comfortably feels in science, first of all, theoretical.
    He has a great memory, great erudition.
    <br><br>

    \tThe nature of \"Berthier\" is manifested in a flexible form of communication, a critical analysis of the surrounding reality, coming from his own ideas.
    It is more convenient for him to obey than to take responsibility.
    <br><br>

    \tHe is a healthy and physically strong, enduring person and a workaholic.
    In his house, in the workplace, in the workshop is always order.
    Material values, money, food, carnal pleasures are of great importance for a carrier of this type.
    <br><br>

    \tHe constantly and easily takes care of households.
    He has few problems with his own health.
    He equips his permanent and even temporary dwelling solidly and joyfully, thoroughly preparing for the repair of housing.
    For money and material values is normal.
    If they are not enough, seeks to earn (earn) in various ways.
    <br><br>

    \tHe is a gentle person in everyday life, peace-loving, benevolent, avoiding conflicts in all areas of life,
    except intellectual disputes and emotional attachments.
    In rare disputes or discussions, hidden, sometimes powerful intellectual cynicism,
    lobality and systematic thinking, accuracy as the quality of the mentality of his mind make themselves felt.
    <br><br>

    \tA man like \"Berthier\" is interested in promoting his ideas and attitudes and dreams of meeting like-minded people with
    pronounced volitional character traits and trust in his leadership abilities.
    In a difficult or extreme situation, he acts decisively and is able to surprise with the adequacy of his actions, will, heroism, courage,
    physical and mental stamina, intellectual power.
    In sports activities is able to reach records and win.
    <br><br>

    \tPeople like \"Berthier\" - long-livers, as they say \"healthy\", rarely get sick and work a lot physically.
    Excellent athletes, owners, parents.
    By vocation - inventors, researchers, doctors, lawyers, consultants, artisans, travelers, conservationists, old people and children.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="PELW_title"> PEWL – Borja </string>

    <string name="PELW_short"><![CDATA[
    \t\"Borgia\" is a holiday person.
    Pleasure, material well-being for her is more important than spiritual and social values.
    In communicating with people, she is the best interlocutor.
    Her emotions are free and adequate to the moment of communication.
    <br><br>

    \tShe is a born actor and lover.
    Her speech is verbose and it is not easy for her to speak in public.
    She is lazy, although in everyday life she prefers to do the main thing herself.
    <br><br>

    \tShe is an insecure person, but in an extreme situation she acts decisively.
    It is more convenient for her to be led.
    She is peaceful and benevolent.
    In the soul and by the vocation of \"Borgia\" - restaurateur, guide, film actor, kind person.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="PELW_full"><![CDATA[
    \tThe carrier of the mental type \"Bordzha\" - the most interesting interlocutor and actor, peace-loving, charming and conducive to communication,
    outwardly attractive and often in his youth a very beautiful person.
    <br><br>

    \tIn her youth and in the first half of her life, she is called the \"man-holiday\", actress, charming handsome, or charming beauty (some kind of vulgarity is noted).
    Pleasure, feast, material well-being for her is more important than spiritual and social values.
    <br><br>

    \tIts internal attitude is:
    <blockquote>- Money, carnal pleasures rule the world.<br>
    - A lot of money does not happen, happiness - in the amount of money and material objects owned.<br>
    - With all you can negotiate with the help of cunning and charm.</blockquote>

    \tCharacteristics of the character and behavior:
    <blockquote>- Mercantilism.<br>
    - The tendency to hoarding and luxury, to the excesses in food.<br>
    - The need to satisfy carnal pleasures.<br>
    - Propensity to take bribes.<br>
    - Survivability, laziness, flaccidity, \"thick-skin\".<br>
    - Idleness.<br>
    - Thoroughness in places of permanent residence.<br>
    - The desire to own property, shoes, accessories, etc.<br>
    - Focusing on one\'s own misunderstanding, and caution in the conclusions.<br>
    - Permanent dispute without result.<br>
    - Fear of public speaking and arguing.<br>
    - Propensity to ask clarifying questions.<br>
    - Verbosity, pauses in conversation.<br>
    - The use of parasitic words, interjections.</blockquote>

   \tTeachers call a student, carrier type \"Bordzha\" logical \"brake\" in the class or group of learning.
   Instead of a simple solution, it offers several difficult ones.
   The passion for mental activity and at the same time hidden rebellion against it determine the complexity and originality of the thinking process.
   <br><br>

   \tSuch a person is not easy to speak in public.
   Sometimes he is jokingly called a talker (if he paws on a public appearance).
   He feels insecure in the logical sphere, in interviews, discussions, concise language, in the choice of one of several possible solutions.
   It is important for him to have people in his community whose advice he can rely on.
   <br><br>

   \tIn ordinary communication, a person like \"Bordzha\" is an excellent conversationalist, wordy, artistic.
   He is an emotionally relaxed man with a good sense of humor.
   His emotions are free and adequate to the moment of communication.
   He is a good actor, easy to trust and is interested in a variety of issues and problems.
   <br><br>

   \tA man like \"Bordzha\" is not self-confident and does not hide it.
   It is more convenient for him to be led, subordinate, sacrificial in everyday affairs and events.
   <br><br>

   \tBy vocation, carriers such as \"Borgia\" are show business actors, theater and film actors, generous lovers, salesmen, realtors, promoters.
   They are practically absent in the scientific community.
   ]]></string>

    <string name="EPLW_title"> EPLW – Bukharin </string>

    <string name="EPLW_short"><![CDATA[
    \t\"Bukharin\" is very emotional, romantic and his mood changes dramatically.
    He often falls in love himself for many - an object for love.
    He is a healthy and enduring person, perhaps a workaholic.
    He is a good caring parent, his house is in order and prosperity.
    <br><br>

    \tHis speech is verbose, and it is not easy for him to speak in public.
    \tHe is an unsure person, but in an extreme situation, he acts decisively.<br>
    It is more convenient for him to be led, he is peaceful and benevolent.

    According to his calling, he is an artist and a universal \"pet\".
    ]]></string>

    <string name="EPLW_full"><![CDATA[
    \tA man of this type is an enthusiastic, romantic, good-natured hardworking.
    His mood often changes.
    He does not know moderation in anything: love, hate, anger, disbelief in his own strength, guilt, fun - such states absorb him entirely.
    <br><br>

    \tMany carriers such as \"Bukharin\" are distinguished by <i>an emotional reaction to events</i>;
    they are vulnerable, a frequent internal theme of their thinking - regret that the world is getting worse, nothing can be done about it.
    But at the same time, contrary to similar reasoning, they are optimistic and cheerful.
    They love to learn and are drawn to knowledge, and the cognitive process in life is present in all spheres of activity.
    <br><br>

    \tA person like \"Bukharin\" has paradoxical logical and literary abilities, an excellent memory for details, he is very talkative and witty,
    able to be an attentive person.
    <i>He listens to the opinions of others and trusts others.</i>
    He is romantic, has a good sense of humor.
    He has an original sense of beauty, an interest in simple art, for example, folklore, pop genre (songs, humor).
    Sometimes sadness comes because of feeling like an ordinary person among others.
    <br><br>

    \t\"Bukharin\" is a healthy and physically strong, enduring man, a caring business executive.
    There is always order in his house, in the workplace, in the workshop.
    Material values, money, food, carnal pleasures for him are of great importance.
    <br><br>

    \tPeople like \"Bukharin\" - \"healthy people\", \"blood and milk\" rarely get sick and work a lot physically.
    Excellent athletes, owners, parents.
    They equip their permanent and even temporary dwelling soundly and joyfully.
    <br><br>

    <i>In a difficult or extreme situation, they act decisively </i> and are able to surprise with the adequacy of actions, will, heroism, courage,
    physical and mental stamina, intellectual power.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="EWLP_title"> EWLP – Ghazali </string>

    <string name="EWLP_short"><![CDATA[
    \t\"Ghazali\" is very emotional, romantic, and his mood changes dramatically.
    He often falls in love.
    He is a responsible, thoughtful, peace-loving, naive democrat with a pronounced dark-colored attitude.
    He is a man of word and honor, a good friend.
    His speech is verbose and it is not easy for him to speak in public.
    <br><br>

    \tIn everyday life, he is not selective, content with small.
    He is healthy, fearless and prone to risk.
    In his heart and vocation, he is a teacher, philosopher, poet, musician, priest, ecologist, revolutionary and organizer with a democratic management style.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="EWLP_full"><![CDATA[
    \tA person like \"Ghazali\" is an enthusiastic, emotional, romantic pessimist - a democrat, easily walking through life.
    He is a man of word and honor, a good friend.

    \tHis mood changes dramatically.
    He is amorous and responsible in relation to the object of love.
    \"Ghazali\" - a person who is confident, peace-loving, benevolent, avoiding conflicts, but doubting the truths.
    It is characterized by the social role of support and lifeguard.
    <br><br>

    \tIts internal attitude is:
    <blockquote>- Freedom is a great value.<br>
    - Beauty and love save the world.<br>
    - Human life is priceless.<br>
    - People should love and respect each other, but in real life in the world is not easy.<br>
    - I need to figure it out in time.<br>
    - I will prove that no more stupid than others.<br>
    - Truth there is.<br>
    - Freedom of choice is the main condition for personal development.</blockquote>

    \tFeatures of internal attitude\'s manifestation in behavior and character:

    <blockquote>- Bright pessimism.<br>
    - Focusing on one\'s own misunderstanding.<br>
    - Silence and caution in the conclusions.<br>
    - Permanent dispute without result.<br>
    - Propensity to ask clarifying questions.<br>
    - Verbosity, pauses in conversation.<br>
    - The use of parasitic words, interjections.<br>
    - The complexity, originality of the process of thinking.</blockquote>

    \tMany carriers of the type \"Ghazali\" are distinguished by an emotional and sometimes somewhat hysterical reaction to the world.
    They are very vulnerable, a frequent internal topic of their thinking is regret that the world is unfair.
    They tend to short depressions.
    They love art and need emotional nourishment through it.
    The creative process is visible in all types of their activities.
    <br><br>

    \tSpeech carrier type \"Ghazali\" verbose, and it is not easy to speak in public.
    Sometimes he is jokingly called a talker (if he paws on a public appearance).
    It is important for him to have people in his community whose advice he can rely on.
    <br><br>

    \tThe material world has a secondary (minor) meaning for it - usually due to its emotionality and hobby more often than philosophical reflections.
    Sometimes for him the material world is perceived not just as a burden, but as something
    what should change (and already because of this global value can not be).
    <br><br>

    \tIn everyday life, a person like \"Ghazali\" is not selective, content with little.
    Leans towards vegetarianism, raw food eating, separate feeding, oriental health practice.
    He is attracted by the culture of the East, traveling to places of Power, has a dream to visit India, Tibet, etc.
    He is healthy, fearless and prone to risk.
    <br><br>

    \tOutwardly very attractive subtlety (iconography) features, slim figure (if there are no hormonal disruptions in the body).
    By vocation \"Ghazali\" - a philosopher, musician, artist, poet, teacher, inventor, researcher, traveler, etc.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="PWLE_title"> PWLE – Goethe </string>

    <string name="PWLE_short"><![CDATA[
    \t\"Goethe\" is a holiday person.
    Pleasure, material well-being for him are very important.
    He is a responsible, thoughtful, peace-loving, principled Democrat with a faint light-colored world view.
    He is a man of word and honor, a good friend.
    <br><br>

    \tHis speech is verbose and it is not easy for him to speak in public.
    He is an unemotional person and his mood often depends on the mood of those around him.
    In the soul and by the vocation of \"Goethe\" - a teacher, politician, priest, ecologist, revolutionary and organizer with a democratic management style.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="PWLE_full"><![CDATA[
    \t\"Goethe\" - a democrat by conviction and an optimist on attitude.
    Freedom as a philosophical value is of decisive importance in its worldview.
    This word, nobility, honor, personal dignity for him are very significant in dealing with other people.
    The bearer of the mental type \"Goethe\" - in his youth, an outwardly attractive, often beautiful, maloemotsionalny person.
    After 40 years, looks older than his years, but traces of past beauty are not difficult to discern.
    <br><br>

    \tCarnal pleasures, festive feast, material well-being are as important as spiritual and social values.
    Often such a person is called a darling of Destiny for the beauty of body and soul.

    \tIts internal attitude is:
    <blockquote>- A lot of money does not happen.<br>
    - Freedom is a great value.<br>
    - Beauty and love save the world.<br>
    - Human life is priceless.<br>
    - People should love and respect each other, but in real life in the world is not easy.<br>
    - Truth exists and is worth searching for.<br>
    - Freedom of choice is the main condition for personal development.</blockquote>

    \tFeatures of internal attitude\'s manifestation in behavior and character:
    <blockquote>- Propensity for hoarding, collecting and luxury, over the years - to excess in food.<br>
    - Survivability, laziness, lethargy.<br>
    - Flaccidity, \"thick-skin\".<br>
    - Thoroughness in places of permanent residence.<br>
    - The desire to own real estate, expensive cars, jewelry, nice clothes and shoes and accessories, etc.<br>
    - Focusing on one's own misunderstanding.<br>
    - Silence and caution in the conclusions.<br>
    - Permanent dispute without result.<br>
    - Fear of public speaking and arguing.<br>
    - Propensity to ask clarifying questions.<br>
    - Verbosity, pauses in conversation.<br>
    - The use of parasitic words, interjections.</blockquote>

    \tThe passion for mental activity and at the same time hidden rebellion against it determine the complexity and originality of the thinking process.
    Such a person is not easy to speak in public.
    It is important for him to have people in his community whose advice he can rely on.
    In everyday life, it manifests itself as an unemotional person, and often his mood depends on the mood of those around him.
    By vocation, a person like \"Goethe\" - a teacher, realtor, lawyer, writer, manager, lawyer, politician, collector, philosopher, etc.
    ]]></string>


    <string name="PEWL_title"> PEWL - Dumas </string>

    <string name="PEWL_short"><![CDATA[
    \t\"Dumas\" is a holiday person, a seducer and an excellent negotiator.
    Pleasure, material well-being for him is more important than spiritual and social values.
    He is often lazy, although in everyday life he prefers to do the main thing himself.
    In communicating with people, he is the best emotional interlocutor with a psychotherapeutic style of influence and influence.
    His emotions are free and adequate to the moment of communication.
    He is a born film actor.
    <br><br>

    \tHe is a capable and, most likely, talented person.
    He dreams of a career, recognition, fame, but his deeds and actions are half-hearted, and he often does not achieve his goals.
    This is from self-doubt.
    He often deceives himself and others - this is his proven tool for self-defense.
    He is a complex person, he often becomes irritated, angry, offended by the whole world, including himself!
    He is a good conversationalist and is interested in a variety of questions.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="PEWL_full"><![CDATA[
    \tThe bearer of the mental type \ "Dumas \" is a most interesting interlocutor and actor, charming and conducive to communication, an outwardly attractive and beautiful person.
    He is a gifted, capable and always somewhat talented person.

    \tA person of psycho-type \"Dumas\" friends are often called \"handsome\" or charming beauty (some kind of vulgarity is noted), a holiday person, an artist.
    Pleasure, feast, material well-being, position in society for him is more important than spiritual and social values.

    \tIts internal attitude is:
    <blockquote>- Money, carnal pleasures rule the world.<br>
    - A lot of money does not happen.<br>
    - Happiness - in the amount of money and material objects owned.<br>
    - With all you can negotiate with the help of personal charm.</blockquote>

    <blockquote>Sensual and sensitive… he is hypnotically attractive and knows it. </blockquote>

    \tIn normal communication, \"Dumas\" - a great companion, artistic, emotional and fascinating shirt - the guy.
    It is characterized by a healthy sense of humor, he is an emotionally relaxed person.
    His emotions are free and adequate to the moment of communication, and he always knows how to say what he needs.
    He is a good actor, easy to trust and is interested in a variety of issues and problems.
    <br><br>

    \tA man like \"Dumas\" is not internally self-confident.
    This basic contradiction and duality is carefully hidden from others.
    Himself is hardly recognized in this duality of attitude, self-interest, ill-will towards people who, as it seems to him,
    they do not understand him - an extraordinary and talented person.
    <br><br>

    \tHe is prone to lies - it is a proven tool for self-defense.
    He sleeps badly at night, <i>dreaming about moving up the career ladder, about recognition and fame.</i>
    But in reality, his actions are often half-hearted, and he often does not achieve his goals in his career.
    This comes from the inner uncertainty of the problematic third will.
    He is a difficult person with a difficult character, it is not easy for him, therefore he is often irritated, revenge, angry, offended by the whole world, including himself!
    In his heart, he remains a vulnerable teenager who needs a kind and wise parent.
    <br><br>

    \tBy vocation, the carriers of the psycho-type \"Dumas\" are often politicians, lawyers, show business actors, theater and film actors, writers,
    salespeople and directors of trading structures, realtors, fraudsters (for example, a marriage scam is a universal and win-win hobby of a given psycho type).
    ]]></string>

    <string name="WLPE_title"> WLPE - Lenin </string>

    <string name="WLPE_short"><![CDATA[
    \t\"Lenin\" - is a born leader - an adventurer and knows that he will execute his decisions at any cost.
    He is ambitious and dreams of a good career.
    He likes to talk and, intellectually dominating, imposes his ideas on others.
    <br><br>

    \tHe rarely listens to the opinions of others and does not trust others.
    Subtle feels the physical condition of loved ones.
    Cares about the well-being of themselves and family members.
    He is an unemotional person and often depends on the mood of others.
    In his heart he is a politician, an ecologist, a revolutionary and an organizer with a dictatorial management style with a faint dark-colored outlook on the world.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="WLPE_full"><![CDATA[
    \tA person like \"Lenin\" is a born leader and, as a rule, strives to fulfill the decisions taken 100%.
    He is ambitious, dreams of a good career, of his party or organization, he goes ahead, he has a hard career and at the same time a caring leader.
    <br><br>

    \tIts internal attitude is:
    <blockquote> - Claim for superiority and power, domination and total control.<br>
     - The material world is imperfect and needs endless transformation for comfort and convenience, and I know how to make it more perfect.<br>
     - There is something wrong with my health and appearance.<br>
     - The well-being of the family and offspring are my main values.</blockquote>

    \tFeatures of internal attitude\'s manifestation in behavior and character:
    <blockquote>- Self-confidence, jealousy.<br>
    - Ambition, egoism, stubbornness.<br>
    - High self-esteem, arrogant behavior.<br>
    - Deviation from social norms.<br>
    - Hypocrisy, suspiciousness.<br>
    - Cleanliness and fastidiousness.<br>
    - Cruelty and over-care about loved ones.</blockquote>

    \tIn normal communication, a carrier like \"Lenin\" is an excellent conversationalist, a little emotional and at the same time fascinating.
    He is a good speaker and is interested in a variety of knowledge.
    He is very talkative.
    The speech is ornate, insignificant, ambiguous, with elements of a magical effect on the audience at the expense of a powerful will and uncritical self-confidence.
    It is characterized by a subtle sense of humor, an original sense of beauty, an interest in complex and unusual art, folklore, oriental dance,
    some spiritual practices.
    <br><br>

    \tA person, a carrier of the type \"Lenin\", subtly feels the physical condition of friends and relatives, as a rule, selflessly takes care of them.
    He himself has problems with his health, but he constantly cares not only about himself, but also those close to him, therefore he is more often inclined towards a healthy lifestyle.
    He carefully hides his external physiological defects.
    <br><br>

    \tHe feels duality and insecurity in relations with the world of material things - everything that relates to the body, appearance, fashion, nutrition, carnal pleasures.
    He fears more than other physical violence and beatings, but is prone to extreme cruelty in a difficult situation.
    He equips his permanent and even temporary dwelling with joy and special meaning; he works in this connection to the point of exhaustion, not knowing the measure.
    Money is very important to him.
    If there are not enough of them, it strives for a minimum (if only it is guaranteed) and is content with small things, hoping, nevertheless, to earn money for the quality life of its family.
    <br><br>

    \tThe man, the carrier of the type \ "Lenin \", positioning itself a touchy, a hypocrite.
    According to his actions, he can be fornication, but he is selective and cowardly, unpredictable in feelings, clean and squeamish at the same time,
    and at the same time risks changing partners and preferences.
    <br><br>

    \tA person who is a carrier of the type \"Lenin\", more often an emotionally relaxed person.
    His emotions are free and adequate to the moment of intercourse, and he always says what he needs.
    Sadness rarely visits him, usually in moments of feeling his ordinary human weakness in front of objective difficulties,
    generated by the surrounding material world (to change which is included in his plans), as well as by virtue of feeling like a \"black sheep\" among people.
    ]]></string>


    <string name="LWPE_title"> LWPE- Lao</string>

    <string name="LWPE_short"><![CDATA[
    \t\"Lao\" is a thoughtful, peaceful man, democratic with a poorly expressed dark-colored attitude, sensible, more trusting in himself than others.
    He subtly feels the physical condition of his relatives.
    Cares about the well-being of themselves and family members.
    He is a little emotional person and often emotionally depends on the mood of others.

    In the soul and in life he is an inventor, a researcher, an ecologist, a traveler, a good friend.
    ]]> </string>

    <string name="LWPE_full"><![CDATA[
    \tA man like \"Lao-tzu\" is thoughtful, balanced, delicate, sensible, prone to logical and philosophical understanding of the world around.
    The thirst for intellectual cognition is one of the main features of his character, and he pays special attention to the cognition of everything new and unusual.
    He trusts himself more than others.
    On important issues, he has his own strong opinion, and it is difficult to convince him.
    <br><br>

    \tHe is a democrat by conviction and an optimist in attitude.
    Freedom as a philosophical value is of decisive importance in its worldview.
    This word and honor are very important in relationships, especially in love and friendship, so more often he is a good friend and family man.
    <br><br>

    \His internal attitude is approximately next:
    <blockquote>- The world is systemic, thought can explain a lot.<br>
    - The world is open to exploration.<br>
    - Everything is predetermined and not by chance, there is a deeper meaning in everything, mediated by cause-and-effect relationships.<br>
    - Freedom is a great value.<br>
    - Freedom of choice is a condition for human development.<br>
    - The material world is imperfect and needs endless transformation for comfort and convenience, and I know how to make it more perfect.<br>
    - There is something wrong with my health and appearance.<br>
    - The well-being of the family and offspring are my main values.</blockquote>

    \tA person, a carrier of the type \"Lao-tzu\", is always interested in various philosophical,
    mathematical models of the world order, mythology, philosophy, psychology in all its diversity.
    Perhaps he is leaning toward asceticism, pacifism, socialism.
    In the case of a high intellectual level of development of his personality and the presence of educational baggage, he feels comfortable in science, above all,
    theoretical.
    He has an excellent memory, excellent erudition, deep, solid knowledge on certain issues, acquired in the process of self-education.
    <br><br>

    \tHis character is manifested in a flexible form of communication, a critical analysis of the surrounding reality, coming from his own ideas;
    inclination to dispute, dogmatism; peremptory and unconditional self-righteousness, promoting their ideas and attitudes.
    <br><br>

    \tA man like \"Lao-tzu\" is self-confident in everyday life, peaceful, benevolent, avoiding conflicts in all areas of life,
    except intellectual disputes and preferences.
    In disputes and discussions, hidden, sometimes powerful intellectual cynicism, globality and systematic thinking, accuracy as the quality of his mentality make themselves felt.
    He is interested in promoting his ideas and attitudes, dreams of meeting like-minded people, creating a team of active, rational and decent people,
    working on the principles of intraprening.
    <br><br>

    \tIn ordinary communication, \"Lao Tzu\" is an excellent conversationalist, a little emotional and a bit boring, seemingly absent-minded.
    Has a great sense of humor, an original sense of beauty, an interest in complex and unusual art, cinema,
    graphics, folklore, oriental dance, some spiritual practices.
    In the company, he is emotionally relaxed, and always knows how to say what is needed.
    Sometimes sadness visits him because of the periodic sensation of his ordinary human weakness in the face of objective difficulties,
    generated by the surrounding material world (partly to change which is included in his plans), as well as by virtue of feeling \"white crow\" among people.
    <br><br>

    \tA man like \"Lao-tzu\" subtly feels the physical condition of friends and relatives, selflessly takes care of them.
    He has problems with his health, he is suspicious, but he constantly cares about him and is leaning towards a healthy lifestyle.
    He carefully hides his external physiological defects.
    Feels divided and insecure in relations with the world of material things - everything that relates to the body, appearance, fashion, nutrition, carnal pleasures.
    <br><br>

    \tHe fears more than other physical violence and beatings, but he is cruel in a difficult or extreme situation.
    He equips his permanent and even temporary dwelling with joy and a special meaning.
    Money is very important to him. If there are not enough of them, it tends to the minimum (if only it is guaranteed) and you are content with small,
    dreaming still earn a high-quality life of his family.
    According to his actions, he is fornication, but selective and cowardly, unpredictable in feelings, clean and squeamish at the same time,
    and at the same time risks changing partners and preferences.
    Success in love is necessary for him.
    <br><br>

    \tIn everyday life, \"Lao-tzu\" appears as an unemotional person, and often his mood depends on the mood of others.
    By vocation, a person like \"Lao –tzu\" is an inventor, researcher, lawyer, traveler, conservationist, children and old people, a sage and an esthete.
    The social role of support, lifeguard, consultant, guru is suitable for him.
    <br><br>

    \tIn an extreme situation, \"Lao Tzu\" acts decisively and is able to surprise everyone (including himself) with the adequacy of actions, heroism, courage,
    physical and mental stamina, intellectual power.
    In an extreme situation or sports activities will be able to reach records and win.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="WPLE_title"> WPLE - Napoleon </string>

    <string name="WPLE_short"><![CDATA[
    \t\"Napoleon\" is a born leader, a purposeful business executive, and you are fulfilling your tasks for one hundred percent.
    He is energetic, hardworking, ambitious, dreams of a good career, going ahead.
    He is on the shoulder of a career manager with a dictatorial management style.
    He rarely gets sick and works a lot physically.
    <br><br>

    \tIn ordinary communication, he is a little emotional and verbose person with a good sense of humor.
    He is emotionally relaxed, emotions are free and adequate to the moment of intercourse, but he does not always know how to say what is needed in public.
    It is important for him to have in his environment consultants, experts, whose advice can be relied upon.
    He is a business executive, a builder, a driver, an athlete, a soldier and a parent in his heart and vocation.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="WPLE_full"><![CDATA[
    \tA man like \"Napoleon\" is a born leader, a purposeful fighter in life style, and performs his tasks one hundred percent.
    He is energetic, hardworking, ambitious, dreams of a good career, is going right through, he is on the shoulder of a career manager.
    Needs consultants and advisers.
    <br><br>

    \tIts internal attitude is:
    <blockquote>- Claim for superiority and power.<br>
    - Dominance and total control.<br>
    - Caring for subordinates and loved ones.<br>
    - Fear of public speaking.</blockquote>

    \tFeatures of internal attitude\'s manifestation in behavior and character:
    <blockquote>- Self-confidence, jealousy.<br>
    - Ambition, selfishness.<br>
    - Stubbornness, aggressiveness.<br>
    - High self-esteem, arrogant behavior.<br>
    - Worship requirement.<br>
    - Focusing on one\'s own misunderstanding.<br>
    - Silence, caution in the conclusions.<br>
    - Permanent dispute without result.<br>
    - Propensity to ask clarifying questions.<br>
    - Verbosity and pauses in conversation.<br>
    - Use of words - parasites, interjections.<br>
    - Logical \"brake\" in the class or group of studies.<br>
    - The passion for mental activity and the hidden rebellion against it.<br>
    - The complexity of the thinking process.</blockquote>

    \tA person like \"Napoleon\" is a healthy and physically strong, enduring person, possibly a workaholic, a good caring leader and a parent.
    In his house, in the workplace, in the workshop is always order.
    Material values, money, food, carnal pleasures for a carrier like \"Napoleon\" are of great importance.
    People like \"Napoleon\" - long-livers, as they say, are healthy, \"blood and milk\", rarely get sick and work a lot physically.
    Excellent athletes, owners, parents, spouses.
    It is very difficult to divorce in marriage.
    <br><br>

    \tIn normal communication, a person like \"Napoleon\" is a little emotional and verbose.
    He is emotionally relaxed, has a good sense of humor; his emotions are free and adequate to the moment of communication, but he does not always know how to say what is needed.
    It is not easy for him to perform in public. Sometimes they jokingly call it chatterbox.
    He feels not confident in the logical sphere, in interviews, discussions, concise formulations, in the choice of one of several possible solutions.
    It is important for him to have in his environment consultants, experts, whose advice can be relied upon.
    <br><br>

    \tPeople like \ "Napoleon \", as a rule, healthy, fearless and prone to risk.
    Externally, in most cases - a stocky, rounded shape with a short neck and a round, bony face.
    A person like \"Napoleon\" is more common among builders, drivers, athletes, military personnel and business executives.
    ]]></string>


    <string name="LEWP_title"> LEWP - Pascal </string>

    <string name="LEWP_short"><![CDATA[
    \tIn his heart and soul \"Pascal\" - an inventor, researcher, systematizer.
    He is often interested in the results of scientific research.
    In communicating with people, he is the best interlocutor.
    His emotions are free and adequate to the moment of communication.
    He is a born actor and psychologist in the everyday sense.
    <br><br>

    \tHe is a capable and, most likely, talented person.
    He dreams of a career, of recognition, of fame, but his deeds and actions are half-hearted, and he often does not achieve his goals.
    This is from self-doubt.
    He often deceives himself and others - this is his proven tool for self-defense.
    It can be difficult for him, so he is often annoyed, angry, offended by the whole world, including himself!
    <br><br>

    \tIn everyday life, he is not selective, content with small.
    \"Pascal\" is healthy, fearless and prone to risk.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="LEWP_full"><![CDATA[
    \tThe person, the carrier of the mental type \"Pascal\" - thoughtful, gifted, capable and, most likely, talented.
    His character is difficult, artistic, prone to logical and philosophical understanding of the world around.
    The pursuit of intellectual knowledge is one of the main features of his personality, and he pays special attention to the knowledge of everything new and unusual.
    Surrounding people do not consider him hardworking, he is prone to laziness, and it may very well be that there is a mess in his wardrobe and room.
    In childhood and adolescence, he often conflicts with loved ones and teachers.
    <br><br>

    \His internal attitude is:
    <blockquote>- The world is systemic and not perfect at the same time..<br>
    - Thought, ideas can explain a lot, and the world is open to exploration..<br>
    - Everything is predetermined and not by chance.<br>
    - There is a deeper meaning in everything, mediated by cause-and-effect relationships.<br>
    - I need to understand this and declare myself, because they do not understand me, and my abilities are still not appreciated by others!</blockquote>

    \tIt is possible that the carrier of the mental type \"Pascal\" - a misanthrope.
    He is tormented by human imperfection, and his own as well.
    He makes ethical claims to the world, and it seems to him that the world offends him.
    He is a vindictive person, but most likely, denies it.
    <br><br>

    \tHe is often interested in various philosophical and mathematical models of the world order, mythology, psychosophy, history in all its diversity.
    He has his own firm opinion on many issues, and it is very difficult to convince him.
    In the case of a high intellectual level of development of his personality and educational baggage he feels comfortable in science,
    first of all, theoretical.
    He has an excellent memory, excellent erudition, original knowledge on certain issues, acquired in the process of self-education.
    <br><br>

    \tThe complex nature of the person carrying the mental type of \"Pascal\" is manifested in:
    <blockquote>- Split, hidden aggressive form of communication.<br>
    - Touchiness embellishing yourself.<br>
    - Critical analysis of the surrounding reality, coming from your own ideas.<br>
    - Propensity to dispute, dogmatism.<br>
    - Peremptory and overconfidence self-righteousness.<br>
    - Promoting your ideas and attitudes.<br>
    - In pursuit of career and professional growth.</blockquote>

    \tIn ordinary communication, the person who bears the mental type of \"Pascal\" is an original interlocutor, quite emotional and erudite, slightly monologue.
    His speech is bright, interesting, incendiary.
    It is characterized by a good sense of humor, satire and sarcasm at the same time.
    An original sense of beauty, an interest in complex and unusual art, his own talent and extraordinary appearance, charisma are conducive to communication.
    He is artistic, emotionally relaxed, his emotions are free and adequate to the moment of intercourse, and he always knows how to say what he needs.
    Sadness often visits such people due to the periodic feeling of their self-doubt, ordinary human weakness in front of objective difficulties,
    generated by the surrounding world order (to transform which is included in his plans), as well as by virtue of the sense of being a \"black sheep\" among people.
    <br><br>

    \tThe man, the carrier of the mental type \"Pascal\" - <i>internally deeply unsure of himself, contradictory in actions</i>.
    He carefully conceals this split from others.
    Himself is hardly recognized in a certain duality of attitude, ill-will towards people who, as it seems to him,
    they do not understand him as an extraordinary and talented person.
    He is prone to lies.
    In the debates and discussions his hidden, sometimes powerful intellectual cynicism, globality and systematic thinking, accuracy as the quality of his mentality make themselves known.
    In his heart, he remains a vulnerable teenager who needs a kind and wise parent.
    <br><br>

    \tPascal in \"Thinking\" wrote:
    <blockquote>A person is by nature trusting, distrustful, timid, courageous… dependent and longing for independence in a state of impermanence, anguish, anxiety.</blockquote>

    \tHe is more interested in promoting your ideas and attitudes and dreams of meeting a like-minded person with pronounced strong-willed traits of character,
    which he could lead (manage).
    He believes in destiny and his special purpose in this world.
    <br><br>

    \tThe material world (money, things) for a person, a carrier of a mental type \"Pascal\", is of secondary importance -
    usually due to their preoccupation with philosophical reflections, and sometimes also due to the fact that the material world is perceived not just as a burden,
    but as something that should either change (and already because of this global value can not be).
    In everyday life, \"Pascal\" is not selective, content with little.
    It is easy to adopt a household version of life, preferences and tastes of a companion for life.
    Set to asceticism.
    <br><br>

    \tIn the diet is easily attached to vegetarianism, syroedenie, separate nutrition.
    He is fond of Eastern health practitioners, he is attracted by the culture of the East, traveling to places of Power; sometimes seeks to visit India, Tibet, etc.
    He is healthy, fearless and prone to risk.
    Cruel and merciless in an extreme situation.
    Outwardly very attractive subtlety (iconography) features, slim figure (if there are no hormonal disruptions in the body).

    By vocation - an inventor, explorer, traveler, dreaming of power, fame and recognition.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="EWPL_title"> EWPL - Pasternak </string>

    <string name="EWPL_short"><![CDATA[
    \t\"Pasternak\" is very emotional, romantic, and his mood changes dramatically.
    He is a born theater actor, often falls in love.
    He is a thoughtful, peaceful and naive democrat.
    <br><br>

    \tHe dreams of a career, of recognizing him as an honest, decent and responsible person.
    He subtly feels the physical condition of loved ones, cares about the well-being of himself and family members.
    He is a good conversationalist and is interested in a variety of information.
    By vocation he is a teacher, poet, artist, protector of the weak, animals, ecologist and traveler.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="EWPL_full"><![CDATA[
    \tThe man, the bearer of the psychotype \"Pasternak\" - an unbalanced, emotional, romantic optimist is a democrat, easily walking through life.
    He is a man of word and honor, a good friend and family man.
    Success in love is necessary for him.
    <br><br>

    \tHis mood changes dramatically.
    He is amorous and responsible in relation to the object of love, so he often enters into a formal marriage and is often divorced.
    He does not know moderation in anything: love, delight, disgust, anger, guilt, fun - all passion absorbs,
    and at such a moment nothing can serve as a deterrent.
    He is a person more often self-confident, peace-loving, benevolent, avoiding conflicts.
    It is characterized by the social role of support and lifeguard.
    <br><br>

    \tIts internal attitude is:
    <blockquote>- The universe is beautiful.<br>
    - Freedom is a great value.<br>
    - Beauty and love save the world.<br>
    - Human life is priceless.<br>
    - People should love and respect each other.<br>
    - The material world is imperfect and needs endless transformation for comfort and convenience.<br>
    - Something is wrong with my health.<br>
    - Family and offspring are core values.</blockquote>

    \tIn character, these attitudes appear as:
    <blockquote>- The pursuit of permanent self-demonstration with emotional overlap.<br>
    - Excessive release of positive and negative emotions.<br>
    - Love, smile (as a powerful tool for interacting with other people).<br>
    - Surface interest in astrology, mysticism.<br>
    - In general, an emotional worldview through the need for music, painting, poetry, theater, cinema, etc.<br>
    - Cleanliness and fastidiousness at the same time.<br>
    - Preference for natural food, clothing made from natural fabrics.<br>
    - Tendency to a variety of diets, wellness practices.<br>
    - Fear of getting sick or fear of having to go to the doctor.<br>
    - Need to relax in nature.<br>
    - The need for prolonged sleep and rest.<br>
    - Exhausting work, the ability to endure overload.<br>
    - Special sensitivity to neighbor.<br>
    - Over-care for significant people.<br>
    - Dual attitude to money and material values, life and nutrition.<br>
    - Permanent arrangement of both temporary and permanent housing.</blockquote>

    \tMany carriers of this type are distinguished by a very emotional and sometimes somewhat hysterical reaction to the world.
    They are very vulnerable, a frequent internal topic of reflection - regret that the world is unfair.
    They tend to short depressions.
    They love art and need emotional nourishment through it.
    The creative process is present in all spheres of life.
    <br><br>

    \tMan psycho \"Pasternak\" subtly feels the physical condition of friends and relatives, selflessly takes care of them.
    He has problems with his health, he constantly cares about him and is inclined towards a healthy lifestyle.
    He carefully hides his external physiological defects.
    He feels duality and insecurity in relations with the world of material things - everything that relates to the body, appearance, fashion, nutrition,
    carnal pleasures, money and things.
    He fears more than other physical violence and beatings, but is prone to extreme cruelty in a difficult situation.
    He equips his permanent and even temporary dwelling with joy and a special meaning.
    He works to exhaustion, not knowing the measure.
    <br><br>

    \tMoney is very important to him.
    If there are not enough of them, it strives for a minimum (if only it is guaranteed) and is content with small things,
    hoping, nevertheless, to earn money for the quality life of its family.
    According to his actions, he is fornication, but selective and cowardly, unpredictable in feelings, clean and squeamish at the same time,
    and at the same time risks changing partners and preferences.
    Positions itself touchy, hypocrite.
    <br><br>

    \tHe is a good conversationalist and is interested in a variety of issues and problems.
    Speech is energetic, assertive and somewhat theatrical.
    Trust other opinions on a variety of issues.
    People, carriers like \"Pasternak\" - are always socially oriented.
    By vocation, they are directors, teachers, politicians with prophetic intonations, actors, poets, musicians, psychologists, priests, etc.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="LPWE_title"> LPWE - Plato </string>

    <string name="LPWE_short"><![CDATA[
    \t\"Plato\" is a capable and, most likely, talented person.
    In the soul and in life he is an inventor, a researcher.
    He is interested in the results of scientific research.
    He is a healthy and enduring person, perhaps a workaholic.
    He is a caring parent, in his house is order and prosperity, or he seeks them as his main values.
    He dreams of a career, recognition, fame, but his deeds and actions are half-hearted, and he often does not achieve his goals.
    This is from self-doubt.
    <br><br>

    \tHe often deceives himself and others - this is his proven tool for self-defense.
    He is a complex person, often annoyed, angry, offended by the whole world, including himself!
    He creates discomfort in communicating with other people, sometimes openly conflicts.
    He is a little emotional person, and his mood often depends on the mood of others.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="LPWE_full"><![CDATA[
    \tThe person, the carrier of the type \"Plato\" is a thoughtful, little emotional, hardworking, economical, gifted, easily trained person.
    In normal communication, he is erudite, uncomplicated interlocutor, dry, unemotional, slightly monologue.
    It is characterized by a sense of humor, satire and sarcasm at the same time.
    <br><br>

    \tThe character of \"Plato\" is difficult, at first glance, inhospitable.
    In childhood and adolescence there were conflicts with relatives and teachers.
    The pursuit of knowledge through a logical understanding of the world and conservatism in views - the prevailing features.
    Surrounding people consider the person of the carrier type \"Plato\" hardworking, intelligent and assiduous, a little bore.
    <br><br>

    \tIts internal attitude is:
    <blockquote>- The world is systemic and not perfect at the same time..<br>
    - Thought can explain a lot, and the world is open to exploration.<br>
    - Everything is predetermined and not by chance.<br>
    - There is a deeper meaning in everything, mediated by cause-and-effect relationships.<br>
    - I work a lot, and I need to understand this and declare myself, because many people do not understand me, and my abilities are still not appreciated by others!</blockquote>

    \tWith age, \"Plato\" is inclined to the materialistic worldview.
    In the case of a high intellectual level of development and educational baggage,
    \"Plato\" comfortably feels in science, both theoretical and practical.
    He has an excellent memory, ingenuity, excellent erudition, original knowledge on certain issues, including in the process of self-education.
    <br><br>

    \tIts complex nature is manifested in:
    <blockquote>- Split, hidden aggressive form of communication.<br>
    - Touchiness embellishing yourself.<br>
    - Critical analysis of the surrounding reality, coming from your own ideas.<br>
    - Propensity to dispute, dogmatism and fanaticism.<br>
    - Peremptory and overconfidence self-righteousness.<br>
    - Promoting your ideas and attitudes.<br>
    - In pursuit of career and professional growth.</blockquote>

    \tHe dreams of moving up the career ladder, of fame, but all of his real actions are often half-hearted,
    and more often it does not reach its goals.
    This is from internal insecurity.
    Looks \"Plato\" as a person dissatisfied with what has been achieved.
    He emphasizes his originality, feeling like a "black sheep" among people.
    <br><br>

    \tHe is prone to lies.
    In the debates and discussions his hidden, sometimes powerful intellectual cynicism, globality and systematic thinking, accuracy as the quality of his mentality make themselves known.
    In his heart, he remains a vulnerable teenager who needs a kind and wise parent.
    He is more interested in promoting your ideas and attitudes and dreams of meeting a like-minded person with pronounced strong-willed traits of character,
    which he could lead (manage).
    <br><br>

    \tThe carrier of the psycho-type \"Plato\" is a healthy and physically strong, enduring person, a good owner.
    Material values, money, food, carnal pleasures for him are of great importance.
    By vocation - an inventor, researcher, athlete, dreaming of power, respect and recognition.
    <br><br>

    \tPsycho-type people \"Plato\" - long-livers, as they say, \"healthy people\", \"blood and milk\" rarely get sick and work a lot physically.
    Excellent scientists, athletes, owners, inventors, caring and at the same time despotic parents.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="EPWL_title"> EPWL - Pushkin </string>

    <string name="EPWL_short"><![CDATA[
    \t\"Pushkin\" - a healthy and enduring person, it is possible that a workaholic.
    He is a caring parent, his house is in order and prosperity, and he aspires to them as his main material values.
    He is very emotional, romantic, and his mood often changes dramatically.
    He often falls in love.
    <br><br>

    \tHe is capable and, most likely, a talented person.
    He dreams of a career, of recognition, of fame, but his deeds and actions are half-hearted, and he often does not achieve his goals.
    This is from self-doubt.

    \tHe often deceives himself and others - this is his proven tool for self-defense.
    He is a complex person, he often becomes irritated, angry, offended by the whole world, including himself!
    He creates discomfort in communicating with other people, sometimes openly conflicts.
    He is an interesting interviewee and is interested in a variety of information.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="EPWL_full"><![CDATA[
    \tThe man, the carrier of the mental type \"Pushkin\" - cheerful, unbalanced, hardworking, gifted and capable.
    He loves life in all its forms.
    Creativity is present in him literally in all activities.
    <br><br>

    \tHe is an energetic, emotional, romantic, unbalanced, explosive man, with good health.
    The mood of \"Pushkin\" often changes dramatically.
    He does not know moderation in anything.
    Love, taste, intellectual delight, disgust, anger, faith and disbelief in their own strength,
    guilt, fun - any passion absorbs him entirely, and at such a moment nothing can serve as a restraining force in his actions and behavior.
    <br><br>

    \tIn humans, the carrier of the psycho-type \ "Pushkin \" - good logical, literary abilities, an excellent memory for details.
    He is cheerful, talkative and witty, ready and listen to the interlocutor.
    Usually, \ "Pushkin \" believes in Destiny, in signs and its special purpose in this world.
    As a consumer of information, he is omnivorous and amateurishly trusting.
    People, carriers of the type \"Pushkin\" - <i>are always socially oriented<i>.
    Sanguine - by temperament in most cases.
    <br><br>

    \tA man of psychotype \"Pushkin\" is internally deeply unsure of himself and this he carefully hides from others.
    Himself is hardly recognized in a certain duality of attitude, ill-will towards people who, as it seems to him,
    they do not understand him - an extraordinary and talented person.
    He is prone to lies.
    <br><br>

    \tHe dreams of moving up the career ladder, of recognition and fame.
    But in reality, his actions are often half-hearted, and he does not achieve the desired goals.
    This comes from inner insecurity.
    He often deceives himself and others - it is a proven tool of self-defense.
    They sometimes create discomfort in communicating with other people without noticing it, and sometimes openly go into conflict.
    He is a difficult person, it is difficult for him, therefore he is often irritated, angry, offended by the whole world, including himself!
    In his heart, he remains a vulnerable teenager who needs a kind and wise parent.
    <br><br>

    \tHe is a healthy and physically strong, enduring person, often a workaholic, caring, despotic leader and parent.
    He always has an order in his house, in the workplace, in the workshop, in the kitchen.
    Material values, money, food, carnal pleasures are of great importance for the carrier of the psycho \"Pushkin\".
    He equips his permanent and even temporary dwelling soundly and joyfully.
    For money and material values is normal.
    If they are not enough, seeks to earn in different ways.
    <br><br>

    \tPsycho-type people \"Pushkin\" - long-livers, as they say \"healthy,\" \"blood and milk\", rarely get sick and work a lot physically.
    Excellent athletes, owners, parents.
    They feel well the physical condition of friends and relatives, selflessly take care of them.
    By profession, they are more often - artists, poets, musicians, actors, cooks, drivers, salesmen, tailors, dreaming of power, fame and recognition.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="ELPW_title"> ELPW - Rousseau </string>

    <string name="ELPW_short"><![CDATA[
    \t\"Rousseau\" is very emotional, romantic and his mood changes dramatically.
    He often falls in love.
    He likes to talk and imposes his ideas on others.
    He rarely listens to others\' opinions and does not trust others.
    <br><br>

    \tHe subtly feels the physical condition of loved ones and caring for the welfare and comfort of loved ones.
    He is an unsure person, but in an extreme situation, act decisively.
    It is more convenient for him to be led.
    He is peaceful and benevolent.
    By vocation he is a poet, artist, ecologist and traveler.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="ELPW_full"><![CDATA[
    \tThe man, the carrier of the mental type \"Rousseau\" - unbalanced, emotional, romantic with elements of tragedy.
    His mood changes dramatically.
    He does not know the measure of anything: love, intellectual delight, disgust, anger, disbelief in his own strength, guilt, fun - any passion absorbs him entirely,
    and at such a moment nothing can serve as a deterrent.
    <br><br>

    \tMany carriers of the psychotype \"Rousseau\" are distinguished by an emotional and sometimes somewhat hysterical reaction to the world, they are often vulnerable,
    the inner theme of their thinking is regret that the world is getting worse.
    They love and are drawn to art, and the creative process in life is present in them in all spheres of activity.
    <br><br>

    \tThe person, the carrier of the psychotype \"Rousseau\", has excellent logical, scientific, literary abilities, an excellent memory for details.
    He is talkative and witty, knows how and listen to the interlocutor.
    Often, listening to the opinions of others, trusts others.
    It is characterized by a romantic mindset.
    <br><br>

    \tIn the usual communication \"Rousseau\" - a great companion, quite emotional and pleasant.
    He has a subtle sense of humor, an original sense of beauty, an interest in complex art, for example, cinema,
    graphics, folklore, oriental dance, some spiritual practices.
    Sometimes sadness visits him because of the periodic sensation of his ordinary human weakness in the face of objective difficulties,
    generated by the surrounding material world, change that is not included in his plans.
    <br><br>

    \tThe person, the carrier of the mental type \"Rousseau\", subtly feels the physical condition of friends and relatives, selflessly takes care of them.
    He has problems with his health, he is suspicious, constantly worried about himself, and is leaning towards a healthy lifestyle.
    He carefully hides his external physiological defects.
    He feels duality and insecurity in relations with the world of material things - everything that relates to the body, appearance, fashion, nutrition, carnal pleasures.
    <br><br>

    \tHe fears more than other physical violence and beatings, but is prone to extreme cruelty in a difficult situation.
    He equips his permanent and even temporary dwelling with joy and a special meaning.
    Money is very important to him.
    If there are not enough of them, it strives for a minimum (if only it is guaranteed) and is content with small things, hoping, nevertheless, to earn money for the quality life of its family.
    According to his actions, he can be fornication, but he is selective and cowardly, unpredictable in feelings, clean and squeamish at the same time,
    and at the same time risks changing partners and preferences.
    <br><br>

    \tThe man, the carrier of the mental type \"Rousseau\", - not self-confident in everyday life, peaceful, benevolent, avoiding conflicts in all areas of life,
    except intellectual disputes and emotional attachments.
    In rare disputes or discussions, hidden, sometimes powerful intellectual cynicism, globality and systematic thinking, accuracy is revealed as the quality of the mentality of his mind.
    He is interested in promoting your ideas and attitudes and dreams of meeting a like-minded person with pronounced strong-willed personality traits.
    and trust his leadership abilities.
    <br><br>

    \tIt is more convenient for him to be led, subordinate, sacrificial in everyday affairs and events.
    He believes in the fate and special purpose of man.
    But in a difficult and extreme situation, \"Rousseau\" acts decisively and is able to surprise everyone (including himself) with the adequacy of actions,
    heroism, courage, physical and mental endurance, intellectual power.
    In an extreme situation, he is able to reach records and win.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="WLEP_title"> WLEP - Socrates </string>

    <string name="WLEP_short"><![CDATA[
    \t\"Socrates\" - a born leader and knows that his decisions will be implemented.
    He is ambitious and dreams of a good career.
    He likes to talk and, intellectually dominating, imposes his ideas on others.
    He rarely listens to the opinions of others and does not trust others.
    He is hardy.<br><br>

    \tHe appears as an unemotional person, but alone with himself he sets free his feelings.
    In everyday life, he is not selective, content with small.
    He is healthy, fearless and prone to risk.
    In his heart he is a politician, manager, the head of a campaign with a dictatorial management style.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="WLEP_full"><![CDATA[
    \tA person who is a carrier of a mental type \"Socrates\" is a born leader and fulfills his decisions as much as possible.
    He is ambitious, dreams of a successful career, about his party or organization, club or his school.
    On the way to the goals goes right through.
    He is on the shoulder of a career manager with a dictatorial leadership style.
    <br><br>

    \tHis character is manifested in:
    <blockquote>- Unflexible form of communication.<br>
    - Critical analysis of the surrounding reality, coming from your own ideas.<br>
    - Propensity to dispute, dogmatism.<br>
    - Peremptory and unconditional self-righteousness.<br>
    - Promoting your ideas and attitudes.</blockquote>

    \tIts internal attitude is:
    <blockquote>- Claim for superiority and power.<br>
    - Dominance and total control.<br>
    - Dispassion and dryness in the expression of emotions is a lifestyle.<br>
    - Strong feelings are unacceptable,
    an open experience in people of deeply seething inside mental states (love, hate, delight, disappointment, etc.).</blockquote>

    \tThe following character traits appear in the behavior:
    <blockquote>- Self-confidence, vanity.<br>
    - Jealousy, ingratitude.<br>
    - Ambition, selfishness.<br>
    - Stubbornness, aggressiveness.<br>
    - Heightened self-esteem, arrogance.<br>
    - Deviation from social norms.<br>
    - Emotional dryness (constrained laughter, nervous tears).<br>
    - Inadequacy in emotional manifestations.<br>
    - The presence of the only (as a rule) object of passion and love.<br>
    - \"Glassy\" stare, exhausting control of the emotional state of their environment.<br>
    - Deeply hidden feelings.<br>
    - Traction to art.<br>
    - Secret activities and tests themselves in poetry, literature, music, painting, theater, etc.</blockquote>

    \tIn normal communication, a person who carries a mental type of \"Socrates\" is a confident and energetic conversationalist, a little emotional and fascinating.
    It is characterized by a subtle sense of humor, an original sense of beauty, an interest in complex art, for example, cinema,
    graphics, oriental dances, some spiritual practices, to modern art.
    <br><br>

    \tThe person, the carrier of the mental type \"Socrates\", is a good speaker, interested in various fields of knowledge and problems.
    His speech is ornate, insignificant, ambiguous, with elements of a magical effect on the audience due to the powerful will and not critical self-confidence.
    In the case of a high intellectual level of personal development and the presence of educational baggage, he feels comfortable in science,
    first of all, theoretical.
    \"Socrates\" has an excellent memory, excellent erudition, deep, solid knowledge on certain issues, acquired in the process of self-education.
    <br><br>

    \tThe material world for a person, a carrier of the mental type \"Socrates\", is of secondary importance due to preoccupation with philosophical reflections.
    In everyday life, he is not selective, content with small.
    In his room, wardrobe, on the table - a working mess.
    He easily adopts the household version of life, style, preferences and tastes of a companion for life.
    <br><br>

    \tLeans towards vegetarianism, raw food eating, separate feeding, oriental health practice.
    He is attracted by the culture of the East.
    Perhaps he tends to asceticism, pacifism.
    <br><br>

    \tHe is healthy by nature, fearless and prone to risk.
    Outwardly very attractive subtlety (iconography) features, slim figure.
    In an extreme situation, he acts decisively, is able to reach records and win.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="WEPL_title"> WEPL - Tolstoy </string>

        <string name="WEPL_short"><![CDATA[
    \t\"Tolstoy\" is a born leader and knows that his decisions will be executed.
    He is ambitious and dreams of a good career.
    He subtly feels the physical condition of people significant to him.
    Cares about the welfare of themselves and loved ones.
    <br><br>

    \tHe is a good conversationalist and is interested in a variety of questions.
    In emotional disputes he dominates.
    In his heart and vocation he is a politician, a priest, an ecologist, a revolutionary and an organizer with a dictatorial management style.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="WEPL_full"><![CDATA[
    \tThe person, the carrier of the mental type \"Tolstoy\", is a born leader and fulfills the decisions taken 100%.
    He is ambitious, dreams of fame, a successful career, his party or organization, school or club.
    To achieve the goal goes ahead, he is on the shoulder of a career manager with a dictatorial management style.
    <br><br>

    \tIts internal attitude is:
    <blockquote>- Claim for superiority and power.<br>
    - Dominance and total control.<br>
    - The material and spiritual world is not perfect and needs endless transformation, and I know how to make it more perfect.<br>
    - There is something wrong with my health and appearance.<br>
    - The well-being of the family and offspring are my main values.</blockquote>

    \tCharacter traits of human, carrier of mental type \"Tolstoy\":
    <blockquote>- Self-confidence, activity.<br>
    - Jealousy, ingratitude.<br>
    - Ambition, selfishness.<br>
    - Stubbornness, aggressiveness.<br>
    - Neglect of other people.<br>
    - High self-esteem, arrogant behavior.<br>
    - Deviation from social norms.<br>
    - Hypocrisy, suspiciousness.<br>
    - Cleanliness and fastidiousness.<br>
    - Over-care about loved ones.</blockquote>

    \tIn normal communication, a person who bears a mental type of \"Tolstoy\" is an energetic conversationalist, quite emotional and pleasant.
    The speech is assertive and somewhat theatrical.
    For \"Tolstoy\" is characterized by a subtle sense of humor, an original sense of beauty.
    He is artistic, emotionally relaxed, his emotions are free and adequate to the moment of intercourse, and he always knows how to say what he needs.
    <br><br>

    \tHe is interested in other people\'s opinions and trusts other views on various issues.
    Sometimes sadness visits him because of the periodic sensation of his ordinary human weakness in the face of objective difficulties,
    generated by the surrounding material world (to change which is included in his plans), as well as by virtue of feeling like a “black sheep” among people.
    <br><br>

    \tHe subtly feels the physical condition of friends and relatives, selflessly takes care of them.
    He has problems with his health, but he constantly cares about him and is prone to a healthy lifestyle.
    He carefully hides his external physiological defects.
    He feels duality and insecurity in relations with the world of material things - everything that relates to the body, appearance, fashion, nutrition, carnal pleasures.
    <br><br>

    \tFears more than other physical violence and beatings, but is prone to extreme cruelty in a difficult situation.
    He equips his permanent and even temporary dwelling with joy and a special meaning.
    Money is very important to him. If there are not enough of them, it tends to the minimum (if only it was guaranteed), but still it’s not content with small,
    dreaming to earn the quality life of his family.
    Ready to work to exhaustion, not knowing the measures, if there is a motivation for fame or good material rewards.
    <br><br>

    \tAccording to his actions, \"Tolstoy\" is lascivious, but selective and cowardly, unpredictable in feelings, clean and squeamish at the same time,
    and at the same time he risks changing partners and preferences.
    Positions itself touchy, hypocrite.
    <br><br>

    \tThe person, the carrier of the mental type \ "Tolstoy \", is interested in various fields of knowledge and philosophical problems,
    demonstrates an interest in complex and unusual art, for example, modern art, folklore, bard art,
    oriental dance, some spiritual practices.
    <br><br>

    \tPeople, carriers like \"Tolstoy\" - are always socially oriented.
    By vocation, they are directors, conductors, film actors, realtors, heads of foundations, organizations, teachers, politicians with prophetic intonations, teachers, priests, etc.
    ]]></string>


    <string name="WPEL_title"> WPEL - Tvardovsky </string>

    <string name="WPEL_short"><![CDATA[
    \t\"Tvardovsky\" - a born leader, a dedicated fighter, and perform their tasks 100%.
    He is healthy, energetic, hardworking, ambitious, dreams of a good career, going ahead.
    He is on the shoulder of a career manager with a dictatorial management style.
    <br><br>

    \tIn ordinary communication, he is an emotional and laconic person.
    Interested in a variety of issues and problems.
    Speech is energetic, assertive, but emotionally trapped.
    By vocation and soul — a builder, driver, athlete, soldier, and good family man — one-sided lover.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="WPEL_full"><![CDATA[
    \tThe person, the carrier of the mental type \"Tvardovsky\", is a born fighter and leader, a purposeful person,
    which in most cases maximizes its plans.
    He is energetic especially in the morning, hardworking, ambitious, dreams of a good career, he goes right through, he is able to cope with his post.
    <br><br>

    \tIts internal attitude is:
    <blockquote>- Claim for superiority and power.<br>
    - Dominance and total control without compromise.<br>
    - Caring for subordinates and loved ones.<br>
    - Dispassion and stability in the expression of emotions as a style of communication.<br>
    - Permissibility due to fear of experiencing in people the manifestation of strong feelings and emotions deeply seething within mental states
    (love, hate, rapture, frustration, etc.)</blockquote>

    \tFeatures of internal attitude\'s manifestation in behavior and character:
    <blockquote>- Self-confidence, jealousy.<br>
    - Ambition, selfishness.<br>
    - Stubbornness, aggressiveness.<br>
    - Heightened self-esteem.<br>
    - Arrogant behavior, Worship requirement.<br>
    - Emotional dryness (constrained laughter, nervous tears).<br>
    - Inadequacy in emotional manifestations and the presence of the only (as a rule) object of passion (love).<br>
    - \"Glassy\" stare.<br>
    - Exhaustive control of the emotional state of people from a meaningful environment.<br>
    - Very deeply hidden feelings.<br>
    - Secret activities and tests themselves in poetry, literature, music, painting, theater, etc.</blockquote>

    \tA person who bears a mental type \ "Tvardovsky \" is a healthy and physically strong, enduring person, as a rule, a workaholic, a caring leader and a parent.
    He always has order in his house, at his workplace, in his workshop.
    Material values, real estate, money, food, carnal pleasures are very important to him.
    In ordinary communication, \"Tvardovsky\" - an ordinary energetic person, a little emotional and laconic.
    He is interested in various, often economic, sports, military topics.
    Speech is energetic, assertive.
    They love the feast and family traditions.
    <br><br>

    \tOutwardly, people like WFEL are more often stocky, round-shaped men and women, with a short neck and a bony face.
    Most of them are long-livers, as they say \ "healthy people \", \ "blood and milk \", rarely get sick and work a lot physically.
    Excellent athletes, owners, family men and parents.<br><br>

    \tPeople with a mental type of \"Tvardovsky\", can often be found among builders, drivers, athletes, military personnel.
    At retirement age, they are actively working in the suburban areas and in the subsidiary farm.
    They love to grow flowers, make food preparations for the winter.
    By vocation they are caring and powerful business executives, athletes, warriors.
    ]]></string>


    <string name="PWEL_title"> PWEL - Chekhov </string>

    <string name="PWEL_short"><![CDATA[
    \t\"Chekhov\" is a holiday person. Pleasure, material well-being for him are very important.
    He is lazy, although at home he tries to do everything himself.
    He is a responsible, peace-loving, naive democrat.
    <br><br>

    \tHe is a man of word and honor, a good friend.
    He appears as an unemotional person, but alone with himself he releases his feelings and experiences.
    He dreams of a career, of recognizing him as an honest, decent and responsible person.
    By vocation and soul he is a restaurateur, politician, realtor, economist, ecologist, teacher, judge, writer.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="PWEL_full"><![CDATA[
    \tThe carrier of the mental type \"Chekhov\" is an outwardly attractive, often beautiful, unemotional, benevolent person.
    He is a democrat by conviction and is more optimistic than a pessimist in attitudes.
    Freedom as a philosophical value is of decisive importance in its worldview.
    <br><br>

    \tThis word, nobility, honor, personal dignity for him are very significant in dealing with other people.
    Carnal pleasures, festive feast, material well-being are as important as spiritual and social values.
    Often such a person is called the darling of fate, the favorite of women (beautiful in both body and soul!).
    <br><br>

    \tIts internal attitude is:
    <blockquote>- Money, carnal pleasures rule the world.<br>
    - A lot of money does not happen.<br>
    - Freedom is a great value.<br>
    - Beauty and love save the world.<br>
    - Human life is priceless.<br>
    - People should love and respect each other.<br>
    - Dispassion and stability in the expression of emotions - style of communication.<br>
    - Display of strong feelings and emotions is unacceptable.<br>
    - It is terrible to experience the deep emotional feelings in public.</blockquote>

    \tFeatures of internal attitude\'s manifestation in behavior and character:
    <blockquote>- Propensity to hoarding, to collecting and luxury, to excess in food.<br>
    - The need to satisfy carnal pleasures.<br>
    - Survivability, \"thick-skin\".<br>
    - Idleness, thoroughness in places of permanent residence.<br>
    - The desire to own property, shoes, accessories, etc.<br>
    - Emotional dryness (constrained laughter, nervous tears).<br>
    - Inadequacy in emotional manifestations.<br>
    - The presence of the only (as a rule) object of passion and love.<br>
    - \"Glassy\" stare.<br>
    - Exhaustive control of the emotional state of people from a meaningful environment.<br>
    - Very deeply hidden feelings.<br>
    - Traction to art.<br>
    - Secret lessons and tests in poetry, literature, music, painting, theater, etc.</blockquote>

    \tBy vocation, a person like \"Chekhov\" is a teacher, realtor, lawyer, writer, manager, lawyer, politician, collector, philosopher, manager in the tourism business,
    chef, film artist, artist, designer, etc.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="LWEP_title"> LWEP - Einstein </string>

    <string name="LWEP_short"><![CDATA[
    \t\"Einstein\" is a thoughtful, peace-loving, democratic person with a poorly expressed dark-colored attitude, a reasonable one who trusts himself more than others.
    <br><br>

    \tHe appears as an unemotional person, but alone with himself he sets free his feelings.
    In everyday life, he is not selective, content with small.
    He is healthy, fearless and prone to risk.
    He is an inventor, a researcher, a traveler, a good friend in his soul and in life.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="LWEP_full"><![CDATA[
    \tThe person, the carrier of the mental type \"Einstein\", is thoughtful, balanced, unemotional, delicate, sensible,
    prone to logical and philosophical understanding of the world.
    The thirst for intellectual knowledge is one of the main features of his nature, and he pays special attention to the knowledge of everything new and unusual.
    When making decisions, he trusts himself more than others.
    <br><br>

    \t\"Einstein\" is democrat by conviction.
    Freedom, as a philosophical value, is crucial in its worldview.
    This word and honor are very important for him in relationships, especially in love and friendship, therefore \"Einstein\" is a good friend and family man, more often one-lover.
    <br><br>

    \tIts internal attitude is:
    <blockquote>- The world is systemic, thought can explain a lot.<br>
    - The world is open to research, everything is predetermined and not by chance.<br>
    - There is a deeper meaning in everything, mediated by cause-and-effect relationships.<br>
    - Freedom is a great value.<br>
    - Dispassion and stability in the expression of emotions is a lifestyle.<br>
    - Display of strong feelings and emotions is unacceptable, an open expression of deep feelings in public (love, hate, delight, disappointment, etc.).</blockquote>

    \tFeatures of internal attitude\'s manifestation in behavior and character:
    <blockquote>- Emotional dryness (constrained laughter, nervous tears).<br>
    - Inadequacy in emotional manifestations.<br>
    - The presence of the only (as a rule) object of passion and love.<br>
    - "Glassy\" stare.<br>
    - Exhausting control of the emotional state of a meaningful environment.<br>
    - Very deeply hidden feelings.<br>
    - Traction to art, secret lessons and tests in poetry.<br>
    - Literature, music, painting, theater, etc.</blockquote>

    \tThe carrier of the \"Einstein\" type is also interested in various philosophical and mathematical models of the world order,
    mathematics, physics, biology, mythology, philosophy in all its diversity.
    On many issues, he has his own firm opinion, and it is difficult to convince him.
    Perhaps he tends to asceticism, pacifism.
    In the case of a high intellectual level of personal development and the presence of educational baggage,
    the carrier of the type \"Einstein\" comfortably feels in science, first of all, theoretical.
    He has an excellent memory, excellent erudition, deep, solid knowledge on certain issues, acquired in the process of education and self-education.
    <br><br>

    \tHis character is manifested in:
    <blockquote>- Flexible form of communication.<br>
    - Critical analysis of the surrounding reality, coming from your own ideas.<br>
    - Propensity to dispute, dogmatism.<br>
    - Peremptory and unconditional self-righteousness.<br>
    - Promoting your ideas and attitudes.</blockquote>

    \t\"Einstein\" - a person, in most cases, self-sufficient, self-confident in everyday life, peaceful, benevolent,
    avoiding conflicts in all areas of life, except for intellectual disputes and preferences.
    In disputes or discussions, hidden, sometimes powerful intellectual cynicism, globality and systematic thinking, make themselves felt,
    accuracy and intellectual domination as the quality of his mindset.
    <br><br>

    \tThe person, the carrier of the mental type \"Einstein\", is interested in promoting your ideas and attitudes, wants to meet like-minded people and create an effective team.
    It is characterized by a subtle sense of humor, an original sense of beauty, an interest in complex and unusual art, for example, cinema,
    graphics, folklore, oriental dance, some spiritual practices.
    He is emotionally constrained.
    Sometimes he is sad because of the periodic feeling of his ordinary human weakness before the objective difficulties created by the surrounding material world,
    and also because of the feeling of a \"black sheep\" among people.
    <br><br>

    \tThe material world for people like \"Einstein\" is of secondary importance.
    Usually, due to their preoccupation with philosophical reflections, and sometimes due to the fact that for them the material world is perceived not just as a burden,
    but as something that should either change (and already because of this global value can not be), or as something that can be donated without much regret.
    In everyday life, they are not selective, as a rule, they are content with little.
    In the room, wardrobe, on the desk they have a working mess.
    To the surprise of others, they sometimes adopt the household version of life, style, preferences and tastes of their companion through life.
    <br><br>

    \tLeans towards vegetarianism, raw food eating, separate feeding, oriental health practice.
    They are attracted by the culture of the East and traveling through the places of the Force; they strive to visit India, Tibet, etc.
    Fearless and risk averse.
    Externally, \"Einsteins\" in most cases, very attractive subtlety (iconographic) features, slimness and grace of the figure, look younger than his years.
    <br><br>

    \tBy vocation, the people of the psychotype \"Einstein\" - scientists, inventors, researchers, travelers, designers, programmers, artists, writers, etc.
    ]]></string>


    <string name="PLEW_title"> PLEW - Epicurus </string>

    <string name="PLEW_short"><![CDATA[
    \t\"Epicurus\" is a holiday person.
    Pleasure, material well-being for him is more important than spiritual and social values.
    He is lazy, although in everyday life he prefers to do the main thing himself.
    In communicating with people, he is the best interlocutor.
    <br><br>

    \tHe appears as an unemotional person, but alone with himself he releases his feelings and experiences.
    Under the influence of alcohol, his emotions are free and he smiles easily.
    He is an unsure person, but in an extreme situation, he acts decisively.
    It is more convenient for him to be led.
    He is peaceful and benevolent.
    In his heart and vocation, he is a friend, a universal favorite, a slightly lazy and hospitable person.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="PLEW_full"><![CDATA[
    \tThe carrier of the mental type \"Epicurus\", in most cases, is an outwardly attractive, often beautiful, peaceful and benevolent interlocutor,
    balanced and unemotional, influenced and weakly character person.
    By temperament - often phlegmatic.
    <br><br>

    \tA person like \"Epicurus\" is often called a holiday man, compared with a teddy big and warm bear.
    A feast in a warm company is the most important pleasure; carnal pleasures, material well-being for him is more important than spiritual and social values.
    <br><br>

    \tIts internal attitude is:
    <blockquote>- Money rules the world, many of them do not happen.<br>
    - Happiness is in owning your own material things.<br>
    - It is more reasonable to live an unobtrusive, even, quiet life, be prudent, loyal and cautious.<br>
    - Dispassion and stability in the expression of emotions - style of communication.<br>
    - Display of strong feelings and emotions is unacceptable.<br>
    - It is very difficult for people to experience deep spiritual conditions inside (soul, love, hate, delight, disappointment, etc.)</blockquote>

    \tCharacteristics of manifestation in the character and behavior of people, carriers of the mental type \ "Epicurus \":
    <blockquote>- Mercantilism.<br>
    - The tendency to hoarding and luxury, to alcohol and excess in food, the need to satisfy carnal pleasures.<br>
    - Predisposition to receive gifts and bribes.<br>
    - Survivability, laziness.<br>
    - Flaccidity, \"thick-skin\".<br>
    - Idleness as a style of behavior.<br>v
    - Thoroughness in places of permanent residence.<br>
    - The desire to own property, expensive spectacular cars, jewelry, clothing, shoes, accessories.<br>
    - Emotional dryness (constrained laughter, nervous tears).<br>
    - Inadequacy in emotional manifestations.<br>
    - \"Glassy\" stare.<br>
    - Exhaustive control of the emotional state of people from a meaningful environment.<br>
    - Very deeply hidden feelings.</blockquote>

    \tIn the usual communication \"Epicurus\" in most cases - an ordinary companion, verbose, little emotional and pleasant.
    Voice is smooth, quiet.
    Friendly conversations (without beautiful speeches), friendly support is not a satisfying life delight for a FLEW-type carrier.
    It has a good sense of humor.
    He is an emotionally dry man, but under the influence of alcohol his emotions are free and adequate to the moment of intercourse, and he always knows how to say what he needs.
    In the company of friends he is darling!
    <br><br>

    \tA person like \"Epicurus\" in everyday life is manifested as an insecure person, and does not hide it.
    It is more convenient for him to be led, subordinate, sacrificial in everyday affairs and events.
    He tries not to take responsibility in large and small matters.
    <br><br>

    \tIn a difficult or extreme situation, \"Epicurus\" acts decisively and is able to surprise everyone (including himself) with the adequacy of actions,
    heroism, courage, physical and mental endurance, intellectual power.
    In an extreme situation, sports activities, he is able to reach records and win.
    <br><br>

    \tBy vocation, people, carriers of the type \"Epicurus\", - politicians (without leadership ambitions), lawyers,
    consultants, realtors, salespeople, security guards, cooks, waiters, travelers, dentists, etc.
    ]]></string>

    </resources>
