<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_1_2_will_title">1 Will - 2 Will.</string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_1_2_will"><![CDATA[
    \tYour partner, unlike you, is set up to constantly discuss and compare him and your desires.
    It can strain you a little, since you do not see the point in such conversations:
    if you have decided something, then this is no longer discussed, you only need the clear consent of your partner, or the same clear refusal,
    to know, rely on partner support or not.
    If the partner supports your decision, then problems usually do not arise - both of you start to fulfill it,
    but if his desire does not coincide with yours, then instead of simply disagreeing and letting you know,
    the partner starts you \ "to persuade \", to seek a compromise.
    This seems unnecessary to you, since you usually do not intend to change your decisions if they are ripe, and such conversations in your opinion are
    just a waste of time and nerves.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tAgree with a partner that your decisions are not negotiable, but in turn, always inform the partner about your decisions.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.5
    ]]> </string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_1_2_physics_title">1 Physics - 2 Physics.</string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_1_2_physics"><![CDATA[
    \tYou may be irritated by your partner’s excessive activity in material matters.
    And the more your partner is trying to draw you into his vigorous activity (repair, rearrangement of furniture, active lifestyle, playing sports),
    the more annoying it causes you.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tTry to negotiate with a partner so that he directs his activity in a different direction.
    In principle, this should not cause any particular difficulties, since your partner respects other people's habits.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.5
    ]]> </string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_1_2_emotion_title">1 Emotion - 2 Emotion.</string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_1_2_emotion"><![CDATA[
    \tDespite the seemingly common strengths, mutual understanding in such a relationship is difficult.
    Despite the fact that your partner, on the one hand, is clearly trying to play along with your emotions, on the other hand, instead of
    just to listen to you silently, and soak up everything like a sponge, he intercepts your initiative, begins to reason,
    asking questions, and trying to change your emotional state on your own.
    And he does it seems to be soft and unobtrusive, but you can be very annoyed by such a reaction to your feelings and emotions:
    you feel like a perfectly normal person who has been confused with an insane and taken to an appointment with a psychiatrist.
    He, on the one hand, listens to you and assents, but on the other - does not take your opinion at all seriously.
    When interacting with other people, this quality - the ability to emotionally adapt to the interlocutor,
    always have the right word or phrase ready in any situation, it may even make you jealous,
    because you yourself are not able to quickly rebuild your inner emotional state.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tTry to understand that in fact your partner does not want to make you ridiculed, it’s just rather difficult for him to understand
    that your emotional state is so serious for you that even the closest people cannot interfere with it.
    Do not try to prove to the partner the importance of your emotional vision of the situation.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.2
    ]]> </string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_1_2_logic_title">1 Logic - 2 Logic.</string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_1_2_logic"><![CDATA[
    \tYou may be somewhat annoyed by the partner’s desire to discuss and discuss topics that you think have already been clarified.
    Your partner\'s love of talking on any topic and his desire to draw you into a dialogue may tire you.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tReport to your partner your unwillingness to engage in lengthy discussions.
    If you are not interested in listening to your partner's ranting, do not listen to them, he will notice it and stop bothering you.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.6
    ]]> </string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_2_1_logic_title">2 Logic - 1 Logic.</string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_2_1_logic"><![CDATA[
    \tYour partner seems to be too categorical and fixated on his point of view.
    It seems to you that such a state of error is erroneous, and therefore you are trying to show your partner and other views on some problem,
    thus striving to broaden his horizons, to become tolerant of views that differ from his own.
    However, the more you try, the less your partner listens to you. Sometimes your attempts make him laugh, and sometimes they annoy him.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tDo not try to soften the categorical nature of your partner, he will never become more tolerant of the opinions of others.
    Find other, more grateful people.<br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.6
    ]]></string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_2_1_physics_title">2 Physics - 1 Physics.</string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_2_1_physics"><![CDATA[
    \tYour partner may seem too passive in everyday matters.
    You sincerely want to improve your (i.e. both yours and yours) material or living conditions, try to engage him in some kind of activity
    (repair, new business, etc.), expect it to pick up your initiative, listen to your advice and recommendations.
    However, the partner sabotages and extinguishes all your undertakings, and begins to act in this area only when he himself decides.
    This may not cause you any special problems if you have the same level of material requests, or your partner\'s requests exceed your own.
    However, if you want something more from life (more income, better housing, better food, etc.), then serious conflicts between you are possible.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tThe best thing for you will be to accept the fact that your partner decides for himself what he needs from material life.
    Do not expect that he will respond to your initiative to improve something in his life in material terms.
    If you manage to get him to do something for you, then only through other functions, and perhaps it will cost you a lot of effort.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.5
    ]]></string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_2_1_emotion_title">2 Emotion - 1 Emotion.</string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_2_1_emotion"><![CDATA[
    \tYour partner seems to be too emotional and a person fixated on his emotions.
    Such obsession causes you a natural reaction - to help the partner with her cope, defuse the situation with a joke, distract the partner,
    show alternative emotional responses.
    However, instead of gratitude for understanding and support, and the desire to cooperate with you, your partner becomes even more stubborn in his opinion.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tDo not try to call a partner for a dialogue if it seems to you that he is obsessed with an idea, or if it seems to you that he is worrying too much about a certain issue.
    It is better to leave him alone, let him \"burn out\" independently.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.3
    ]]></string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_2_1_will_title">2 Will - 1 Will.</string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_2_1_will">@string/pseudo_philia_1_2_will</string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_3_4_emotion_title">3 Emotion - 4 Emotion.</string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_3_4_emotion"><![CDATA[
    \tAt first, you do not touch the weakness of the partner in the emotional sphere.
    As a rule, at the initial stage you are attracted by its higher functions.
    However, over time, a lack of emotionality begins to affect your relationship.
    Your partner seems to you too emotional, indifferent, too inattentive to you and your feelings.
    When you need emotional support, a kind word, emotional attention, your partner cannot help you in any way.
    He does not understand your need at all and does not see the problem in your experiences.
    And even when, in response to your persistent unconscious provocations, he finally gives out some kind of emotional reaction, it turns out to be too weak,
    to satisfy you.
    <br><br>

     \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
     \tDo not demand from the partner the impossible.
     He will never be able to be sensitive and attentive enough for you anyway.
     Perhaps the best option for you will be to periodically communicate with people who have the 2nd emotion.
     Such communication can charge you with optimism and faith in yourself for a while.
     <br><br>

     \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.2
    ]]> </string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_3_4_will_title">3 Will - 4 Will.</string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_3_4_will"><![CDATA[
    \tSometimes it seems to you that your partner never wants anything at all.
    You are lacking from it initiatives.
    And it is very difficult.
    In fact, your partner is set up such a regime: you express a desire, and he either agrees with him or does not agree.
    Therefore, in order to reach agreement, it is enough just to clearly express your desire out loud, but you do not always succeed, because you yourself are determined to
    so that the partner himself will find out your desire with constant questions.
    But even if you concentrated and still directly expressed your desire, your partner is not always ready to support him, this doubly hurts you.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tTry to learn to clearly and clearly express your desires and do not take the partner’s refusal to fulfill this desire as a personal insult.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.1
    ]]> </string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_3_4_logic_title">3 Logic - 4 Logic.</string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_3_4_logic"><![CDATA[
    \tWhen you once again begin to doubt some opinion, assessment, judgment, and seek the support of a partner,
    he is surprised and does not understand why there is so much fuss on such an insignificant matter.
    In the best case, you get the feeling of insignificance of your throwing.
    At worst - you are left alone with your doubts without the support of a partner and feel lonely and abandoned.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tDo not demand from the partner the impossible, he most likely will never be able to dispel your doubts in the form
    in which you need it.
    Share your doubts in other people with whom you can find support.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.2
    ]]> </string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_3_4_physics_title">3 Physics - 4 Physics.</string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_3_4_physics"><![CDATA[
    \tIn material matters, you really need support and complicity.
    You are trying to attract a partner to clarify your physical needs, expect an initiative from him in these matters.
    However, in practice, your partner himself expects initiative from you - he expects specific requests from you, instead of unintelligible complaints.
    It seems to you that he is too indifferent to you, you would like him to be more caring and attentive.
    You want to get more information from him in practical matters, discuss your fears in the physical sphere with him.
    (concerning health, well-being, appearance of financial well-being, etc.).
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tDo not try to demand from the partner the impossible, he is really not interested in your physical details.
    Try to find such people for communication, which would fill this gap in your relationship (financial adviser, doctor, dressmaker, hairdresser, etc.).
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.2
    ]]> </string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_4_3_physics_title">4 Physics - 3 Physics.</string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_4_3_physics"><![CDATA[
    \tAt the initial stage of your relationship, your partner attracts you with his activity in material matters:
    he seems bright to you, looking after his appearance, active, practical and well-versed in the material world.
    However, after some time you discover that all of its materiality is a soap bubble,
    which bursts when confronted with the slightest physical problems.
    Your partner is not confident in matters of finances, life, appearance, lifestyle, etc.
    He is constantly worried about this, but what specifically he wants - he cannot formulate.
    You would like your partner to take care of your physical condition, and sometimes
    he even begins to take such an initiative - for example, he may start treating you, but he often does everything ineptly and uncertainly, which may annoy you.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tDo not dismiss your partner's conversations on various material, everyday topics, they are really important for him.
    Do not say that \"all this is nonsense and you should not worry about it\".
    For him, this is not really nonsense, but very important questions.
    If you can not help, then at least just listen to his complaints.
    Try to reassure him using other higher functions.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.3
    ]]> </string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_4_3_logic_title">4 Logic - 3 Logic.</string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_4_3_logic"><![CDATA[
    \tIt\’s hard for you to understand your partner when he starts to cling to terms and definitions
    to seek out illogicalities and contradictions in other people\'s statements, to engage in arguments,
    and then get upset if his opponents defeated him.
    It seems to you that he himself is looking for adventures and difficulties, and he is worrying too much,
    that someone might find him not a very smart person.
    You want to help your partner, calm him down, and it seems to you that the phrases: \"Yes, come on!\", \"You shouldn’t worry\", \"Well, who knows what? \".
    In fact, such \"comfort\" even more upset your partner.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tTry to understand that for a partner his experiences are really very serious.
    Every time he starts to \"steam\" about his mental abilities, try to get to the heart of the matter,
    in the understanding of which the partner had a problem, do not be lazy to discuss it, express your opinion,
    discuss alternative opinions.
    Sometimes it is enough to hold such conversations periodically in order to instill in the partner peace of mind that he has enough reserves for until the next crisis.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.3
    ]]> </string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_4_3_emotion_title">4 Emotion - 3 Emotion.</string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_4_3_emotion"><![CDATA[
    \tYour partner may seem like an interesting and emotional person.
    However, some time after the start of communication, it turns out that behind this emotionality there is in fact a very big self-doubt.
    The partner is hinting, then openly begins to demand from you emotional support, participation in their emotional experiences.
    It seems stupid and superfluous to you, and with time it may even begin to annoy.
    Your attempts to reassure your partner turn out to be untenable.
    You feel that you are clearly unable to help your partner.
    At the same time, he may try to influence your emotional state - start joking, make laugh, but he does it awkwardly and at the slightest hint on your part,
    that you do not like it, can be offended and withdraw into itself.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tAlthough really you can not help a partner, but try to at least just listen to his complaints, not waving from them.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.3
    ]]> </string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_4_3_will_title">4 Will - 3 Will.</string>

    <string name="pseudo_philia_4_3_will"><![CDATA[
    \tYour partner may annoy you with your unwillingness to clearly state your desires and unwillingness to take initiative and take responsibility.
    You expect clear and intelligible decisions from him, and he constantly doubts what he wants and tries to call you to dialogue,
    which seems senseless to you - you are too lazy to solve a puzzle every time: \"what does your partner really want \",
    and you would like him to solve this for himself, and he set you up as a guide to action.
    Your partner in your eyes looks like an extremely unreliable person, because at first he can say out loud one decision, and after a while - another.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tWhen your partner speaks about his decision, ask again and clarify whether it is final and sure of his desire.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.1
    ]]> </string>

</resources>