<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="eros_1_3_will_title">1 Will - 3 Will.</string>

    <string name="eros_1_3_will"><![CDATA[
    \tYour partner is too capricious for you, on the one hand he takes offense at you for constantly making some decisions,
    on the other hand, he himself is not able to take any decision at all.
    But even if you reach a compromise in some decision, your partner will remind you on occasion,
    that it was your initiative, and in case of failure, he will definitely reproach this.
    This state of affairs can annoy you a lot.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tNever speak directly about your desires and decisions, always first ask your partner what he would like.
    As a rule, he himself will not answer you intelligibly, but the atmosphere of the discussion will calm him down.
    After that, offer him several options and draw in the favorable light the one that you yourself have already accepted.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.
    ]]> </string>

    <string name="eros_1_3_emotion_title">1 Emotion - 3 Emotion.</string>

    <string name="eros_1_3_emotion"><![CDATA[
    \tYour partner seems to you an unbalanced and emotionally unstable person,
    who can not and does not want to learn to cope with their emotional state.
    Your partner may show offense to you, withdraw into himself, occasionally agreeing to clarify the relationship,
    and even then, only to accuse you of callousness and insensitivity.
    Such reproaches can offend you very much, because in fact you are not at all stale,
    and vice versa. The only problem is that you are not able to convey to your partner your feelings so that he believes in them.
    Sometimes it seems to you that you are walking through a minefield, communicating with your partner on those topics that really concern you.
    Sometimes your first natural emotional reaction to an event or information may cause your partner to have a completely unpredictable and inadequate reaction.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tTry to control your emotional expressions.
    Remember that your partner is very emotional.
    Track and memorize the list of \ "forbidden topics \", on which you should not express your point of view.
    Make yourself a list of phrases that are guaranteed to reassure your partner: \"I love you!\", \"You are the most wonderful!\",
    \"How cool you thought of everything!\". Pronounce them when it seems to you that your partner is waiting for this
    (over time, you can learn to define it), even if you are not currently experiencing the emotional need to pronounce them and you think that your words will sound fake.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.
    ]]> </string>

    <string name="eros_1_3_physics_title">1 Physics - 3 Physics.</string>

    <string name="eros_1_3_physics"><![CDATA[
    \tAt first, this relationship seems quite normal to you.
    Your partner is rather timid in material matters, he is afraid of burdening outsiders with his own problems.
    Comfortability for you in such a relationship depends entirely on how your partner is ready to \"sacrifice himself\".
    Moreover, these victims will be exclusively in his head; from your point of view, you don’t demand any sacrifices from him.
    A partner may suddenly begin to complain about your egoism, that he does not receive any help from you.
    He can annoy you with his constant contrived domestic problems, worries about his appearance, finances, etc.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tTake it seriously and try to respond to complaints and requests from your partner for physical assistance.
    For him, this is not a trifle, but a really serious problem.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.
    ]]> </string>

    <string name="eros_1_3_logic_title">1 Logic - 3 Logic.</string>

    <string name="eros_1_3_logic"><![CDATA[
    \tYour partner sometimes seems unnecessarily picky and mistrustful of your words,
    unable to assimilate one single correct point of view on any matter and calm down on this.
    You may be annoyed by his attempts to draw you into an argument or reasoning on issues in which you have already decided everything for yourself.
    He may begin to criticize your statements, disagree with your opinion, without offering any opinion in return.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tTake seriously the feelings of your partner about the consistency of his statements, about the consistency of any information at all.
    For him, this is really a problem that he wants to discuss.
    In any conversations, it is important to him not only your opinion on a certain issue, but also an explanation of why you came to this conclusion.
    Try to remember this, and do not be lazy to explain the course of their thoughts.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.
    ]]> </string>

    <string name="eros_2_4_logic_title">2 Logic - 4 Logic.</string>

    <string name="eros_2_4_logic"><![CDATA[
    \tYour partner cannot adequately support your passion for reasoning on various topics.
    He wants specifics - your clear opinion on any issue, and you - the process, talk, discuss and come to some opinion together.
    It may seem to you that the partner does not respond enough to your offer to talk and underestimates you in this regard.
    <br><br>

     \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
     \tDo not try to talk to your partner, it is better if you find yourself a more suitable interlocutor.
     <br><br>

     \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.5
    ]]></string>

    <string name="eros_2_4_will_title">2 Will - 4 Will.</string>

    <string name="eros_2_4_will"><![CDATA[
    \tYour partner does not like to take the initiative and is waiting for it from you.
    You want to clarify the goals of the partner, coordinate with yours, show attention to the wishes of the partner,
    and your partner takes your questions with bewilderment and some annoyance.
    You do not feel that you are in demand in this matter, which is somewhat disappointing.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tTake the initiative in your own hands, do not ask your partner what he wants, better tell him what you want,
    and immediately proceed to the realization of his desire. If the partner likes your intention, he will join you and will help you,
    if not, do not try to change your decision along the way, trying to adjust to the partner’s wishes,
    because in this case, you will look like a man in the eyes of a partner who himself does not know what he wants,
    which means unreliable person, i.e. whose decisions cannot be relied upon.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.7
    ]]></string>

    <string name="eros_2_4_physics_title">2 Physics - 4 Physics.</string>

    <string name="eros_2_4_physics"><![CDATA[
    \tYour partner seems to you unnecessarily fussy in material matters.
    Instead of just taking and doing something (or not doing it), he begins to talk about this topic, asking for your opinion that you may be tired.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tAsk your partner to more clearly state their proposals, without any further discussion.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.5
    ]]></string>

    <string name="eros_2_4_emotion_title">2 Emotion - 4 Emotion.</string>

    <string name="eros_2_4_emotion"><![CDATA[
    \tIt is difficult for you to influence the emotional state of a partner when, for example, in your opinion, he is sad or worries about something.
    You are set up to discuss and adjust emotionally, but your partner does not need this.
    Therefore, it seems to you that your efforts are being wasted, and this disappoints you, you feel unclaimed.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tRespect the emotional state of your partner, do not try to \"save\". Interact with him through other functions.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.5
    ]]></string>

    <string name="eros_3_1_will_title">3 Will - 1 Will.</string>

    <string name="eros_3_1_will"><![CDATA[
    \tYour partner initially attracts you with confidence in his desires, in what he wants from life and how he achieves the desired,
    it may seem to you that when you get close to your partner, it will also apply to your desires in the same way, but after a while it turns out
    that your opinion is completely ignored.
    Even if suddenly in your desires there is disagreement, and you express it, expecting concessions and compromises,
    your partner leaves from the discussion, just doing everything in their own way.
    He can explain to your reproaches that he did everything for the good of both of you, but in your eyes his actions look like egoism and unwillingness to listen to your opinion.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tThis is a very difficult relationship, first of all for you.
    Try to convey to your partner that it is important for you to follow a certain ritual before he makes any decision:
    so that he utters certain phrases: \"How do you feel about if we act in this way…\", \"Would you mind…\", etc.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="eros_3_1_emotion_title">3 Emotion - 1 Emotion.</string>

    <string name="eros_3_1_emotion"><![CDATA[
    \tYou may have mixed feelings for your partner:
    on the one hand, he seems to you to be an egoist, not caring about your feelings and emotions, and on the other hand,
    you want to be as confident in everything that concerns the sphere of emotions, relationships, the spiritual side of life, etc.
    This is a very painful relationship, first of all for you.
    It may seem to you that the partner’s emotionality will help you to relax, to become more self-confident,
    however, the partner does not help you cope with your experiences, but instead tries to dictate your own.
    This situation may disappoint you very much in your partner, from time to time you even doubt the truth of his feelings towards you.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tThe main burden on the normalization of relations will have to take on your partner.
    You just need to understand and believe that in fact your partner is not an egoist, and that, in your opinion,
    \"emotional insensitivity\" actually is not, it is just his inherent style of behavior, which he almost can not change.
    <br><br>

     \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="eros_3_1_logic_title">3 Logic - 1 Logic.</string>

    <string name="eros_3_1_logic"><![CDATA[
    \tYour partner, on the one hand, attracts you with its self-righteousness,
    on the other hand, you really miss the explanation from him about how he got this confidence,
    and why he is so self-righteous.
    Your attempts to learn this, or, even worse, your doubts and criticism of such confidence can lead to serious problems in the relationship.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tDo not argue with a partner and do not criticize his manner of expression, ask him, if possible, to argue his opinion.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="eros_3_1_physics_title">3 Physics - 1 Physics.</string>

    <string name="eros_3_1_physics"><![CDATA[
    \tThis is a difficult relationship for you.
    Your partner seems to you to be an egoist who cares only about his own welfare and his needs.
    You try to periodically draw his attention to yourself, your needs and desires, but you do it very ineptly,
    because it is difficult for you to formulate what you really want and what exactly you are experiencing discomfort.
    Of great importance is how comfortable your relationship will be with your previous experience, for example, those received in a family,
    or with other partners and how much your experience coincides with the material needs of your partner.
    If they match - the relationship will be less uncomfortable for you.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tTry to articulate your complaints and complaints, do not be afraid to discuss your problems,
    relating to life, health, appearance, material support, etc. with a partner.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="eros_4_2_physics_title">4 Physics - 2 Physics.</string>

    <string name="eros_4_2_physics">@string/eros_2_4_physics</string>

    <string name="eros_4_2_will_title">4 Will - 2 Will.</string>

    <string name="eros_4_2_will"><![CDATA[
    \tYou expect a clear decision from the partner and a clear expression of your desires,
    however, your partner almost never says directly what he wants, always first trying to find out from you
    what are your desires and intentions to adapt to them.
    It makes you doubt the reliability of the partner, because people who do not speak directly about their decisions, do not cause you to trust.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tAsk your partner to always clearly state your decisions, explain to him that it is easier for you to choose one of the already formulated decisions,
    than take the initiative and offer something of their own.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.5
    ]]></string>

    <string name="eros_4_2_logic_title">4 Logic - 2 Logic.</string>

    <string name="eros_4_2_logic"><![CDATA[
    \tYou do not quite understand why there is so much to talk about topics that are not worth it.
    For some time you can still maintain a dialogue with a partner, but rather quickly you get tired of it,
    since there are many more interesting and important things in the world than clarifications on the tenth circle of accuracy and legitimacy of some judgment.
    Talk partner can make you feel annoyed.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tExplain to your partner that it’s difficult for you to spend so much time talking.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.5
    ]]></string>

    <string name="eros_4_2_emotion_title">4 Emotion - 2 Emotion.</string>

    <string name="eros_4_2_emotion"><![CDATA[
    \tВYou may be a little bored with your partner, he may seem hypocritical and insincere in his emotions, because he does not express directly what he feels.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tAccept your partner as you are.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 0.5
    ]]></string>

</resources>