<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="agape_1_4_will_title">1 Will - 4 Will.</string>

    <string name="agape_1_4_will"><![CDATA[
    \tYour partner is attracted by its lack of capriciousness.
    When you express your wish, your partner always clearly responds, he agrees with him, or he disagrees.
    Either \"yes\", or \"no\".
    At the same time, if the partner said \"yes\", this means that you have acquired a reliable assistant in the fulfillment of your desire.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tНе критикуйте партнера за безынициативность, лучше лишний раз напомните ему о своем желании.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 1.
    ]]> </string>

    <string name="agape_1_4_emotion_title">1 Emotion - 4 Emotion.</string>

    <string name="agape_1_4_emotion"><![CDATA[
    \tIn this relationship, you can fully open up and be yourself, do not hesitate to your feelings.
    You are pleased when a partner responds to your emotional perception of life, mirrors it.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tBe yourself.
    Do not be jealous if you suddenly notice that your partner reacts in the same way to the emotional manifestations of other people.
    In fact, if something binds you (except for your emotionality), then this is not a reason for jealousy.
    Your partner is quite inspired by other people\'s emotions, but as soon as he returns to your influence, everything will continue:
    he will listen to your emotional evaluations and you will guide the emotional background in your relationship.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 1.
    ]]> </string>

    <string name="agape_1_4_logic_title">1 Logic - 4 Logic.</string>

    <string name="agape_1_4_logic"><![CDATA[
    \tYour partner attracts you with his property to listen to your opinion, on the other hand,
    you like it when a partner is able to absorb the essence of your conversations and express your own thoughts, but only more briefly.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tDo not insult your partner, if it seems to you that he misunderstood you the first time, have patience and repeat your thought.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 1.
    ]]> </string>

    <string name="agape_1_4_physics_title">1 Physics - 4 Physics.</string>

    <string name="agape_1_4_physics"><![CDATA[
    \tYour partner attracts you because he does not interfere in the sphere of your material interests, allows you to define your own needs.
    Moreover, the partner actively supports your interests in the physical sphere, adapts to them and actively helps.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tDo not flatter yourself about the willingness of a partner to come to help and do not abuse him, because somewhere above in your partner
    the bases \"Will\" and \"Logic\" are located, which will actively turn on if your partner thinks that you have gone too far.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 1.
    ]]> </string>

    <string name="agape_2_3_logic_title">2 Logic - 3 Logic.</string>

    <string name="agape_2_3_logic"><![CDATA[
    \tYour partner attracts you by constantly provoking you to various discussions,
    at the same time, you are given the opportunity to play the role of lead, i.e. You are in such discussions more competent and knowledgeable.
    This state of affairs, although it requires maximum concentration from you, allows you to fully demonstrate your abilities and therefore gives you great pleasure.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tYour partner can sometimes be caustic and picky in various situations. Remember your leading role and do not be offended by your partner,
    if he starts to slander and catch you on logical inconsistencies.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 1.
    ]]> </string>

    <string name="agape_2_3_will_title">2 Will - 3 Will.</string>

    <string name="agape_2_3_will"><![CDATA[
    \tThe initial stage of your relationship is greatly influenced by the experience of your partner’s previous relationship.
    If life constantly confronted a partner with people who disregarded his desires, then the partner can be incredulous in dealing with you,
    looking for dirty tricks in your attitude.
    In this case, you will have to make a lot of efforts to prove to him that he should not be afraid of infringement of his rights on your part.
    Over time, your partner will begin to trust you and will be happy to respond to your initiative in realizing your desires.
    <br><br>

     \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
     \tBe patient.
     <br><br>

     \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 1.
     ]]> </string>

    <string name="agape_2_3_emotion_title">2 Emotion - 3 Emotion.</string>

    <string name="agape_2_3_emotion"><![CDATA[
     \tYour partner is a very emotional person.
     And you, like anyone else, are able to help him gain self-confidence in emotional terms.
     Over time, your partner will be able to become your most devoted and appreciative friend,
     gradually adopting your views and ways of emotional interaction with the outside world.
     <br><br>

     \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
     \tAll responsibility for the emotional sphere lies with you.
     Pay maximum attention to the emotional state of the partner.
     Try to make sure that the partner does not have reasons for jealousy, if you have to in this way \"comfort\" someone third.
     <br><br>

     \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 1.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="agape_2_3_physics_title">2 Physics - 3 Physics.</string>

    <string name="agape_2_3_physics"><![CDATA[
    \tYour partner is very sensitive to problems in the material sphere and therefore he will be very grateful to you for your practical advice, recommendations and assistance.
    In the face of a partner, you will find a faithful assistant in your endeavors, it will be easy to persuade him to work together.
    He will be happy to learn from you, gradually adopting your everyday habits and lifestyle.
    <br><br>

     \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
     \tDo not criticize your partner for his faults in everyday life, his appearance, attitude to their own health.
     Better help with practical advice and be sure to praise for what you can praise.
     <br><br>

     \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 1.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="agape_3_2_emotion_title">3 Emotion - 2 Emotion.</string>

    <string name="agape_3_2_emotion"><![CDATA[
     \tYour partner is perfect for you in the emotional field.
     This is the person who accepts you as they are, is able to dispel your fears and concerns,
     at the right moment to give you confidence and instill optimism.
     <br><br>

     \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
     \tListen to the opinions and recommendations of your partner emotionally and trust him.
     <br><br>

     \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 1.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="agape_3_2_logic_title">3 Logic - 2 Logic.</string>

    <string name="agape_3_2_logic"><![CDATA[
    \tYour partner is always ready to support your opinion, to detail it and even to speculate for you.
    This calms you down and gives you confidence.
    Uncategorized judgments of a partner, flexibility and variability of thoughts relax,
    helps you to declare your opinion with greater confidence without fear of a categorical negative assessment.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tTrust the partner.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 1.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="agape_3_2_will_title">3 Will - 2 Will.</string>

    <string name="agape_3_2_will"><![CDATA[
    \tYour partner is always sensitive to your desires, and before taking any initiative, is always interested in your opinion.
    He is inclined to seek a compromise and adapt himself to your desires, at the same time he does not
    require excessive initiative from you and if he sees that you hesitate,
    always ready to take it into your own hands, having previously accepted your consent to that.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tTrust your partner, do not be afraid to talk with him about your desires and doubts.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 1.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="agape_3_2_physics_title">3 Physics - 2 Physics.</string>

    <string name="agape_3_2_physics"><![CDATA[
    \tYour partner can be your real helper and protector in the material world.
    You can not fear to complain to him about your difficulties in this area.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tListen carefully to his recommendations and advice, discuss your doubts and fears with him.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 1.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="agape_4_1_physics_title">4 Physics - 1 Physics.</string>

    <string name="agape_4_1_physics"><![CDATA[
    \tIn your partner you are attracted by his confidence in the material world, in his material needs.
    Your partner seems to you reliable, firmly standing on his feet, firmly understanding what he wants from life in material terms,
    constantly \"broadcasts\" this confidence so that it is transmitted to you.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tLet your partner be yourself in his physical habits and tastes.
    It will be easy for you to adjust to it if there are no other people who are authoritative for you in material matters between you.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 1.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="agape_4_1_will_title">4 Will - 1 Will.</string>

    <string name="agape_4_1_will"><![CDATA[
    \tYour partner attracts you with the ability to make decisions and act when he has a desire.
    At the same time, he saves you from having to take the initiative.
    As a rule, he offers something, and you just have to choose whether to agree or not.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tDo not criticize the decisions of your partner.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 1.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="agape_4_1_emotion_title">4 Emotion - 1 Emotion.</string>

    <string name="agape_4_1_emotion"><![CDATA[
    \tEmotional sphere means relatively little for you and therefore if you chose this partner, most likely,
    guided not by his emotionality, but by some other criteria.
    However, your partner attracts you with his emotional brightness.
    You do not get bored with him, he entertains you, making your life emotionally rich and diverse.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tTake your partner\'s emotional state seriously.
    For him, it is really very important.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 1.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="agape_4_1_logic_title">4 Logic - 1 Logic.</string>

    <string name="agape_4_1_logic"><![CDATA[
    \tAt the same intellectual and cultural level, your partner attracts you with the ability to clearly and distinctly express your opinion on any issue.
    You like that your partner has his own opinion on almost any issue, and you like the confidence with which he expresses this opinion.
    <br><br>

    \t<b>Recommendations for interaction:</b><br>
    \tDo not criticize your partner for categorical statements.
    <br><br>

    \tThe ratio of mutual complementarity: 1.
    ]]></string>

</resources>